<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


 <string name="sadeyelyrics">
  With your mercury mouth in the missionary times\n
  And your eyes like smoke and your prayers like rhymes\n
 And your silver cross, and your voice like chimes\n
 Oh, who among them do they think could bury you?\n
 With your pockets well protected at last\n
 And your streetcar visions which you place on the grass\n
 And your flesh like silk, and your face like glass\n
 Who among them do they think could carry you?\n
 Sad-eyed lady of the lowlands\n
 Where the sad-eyed prophet says that no man comes\n
 My warehouse eyes, my Arabian drums\n
 Should I leave them by your gate\n
 Or, sad-eyed lady, should I wait?\n

 With your sheets like metal and your belt like lace\n
 And your deck of cards missing the jack and the ace\n
 And your basement clothes and your hollow face\n
 Who among them can think he could outguess you?\n
 With your silhouette when the sunlight dims\n
 Into your eyes where the moonlight swims\n
 And your matchbook songs and your gypsy hymns\n
 Who among them would try to impress you?\n
 Sad-eyed lady of the lowlands\n
 Where the sad-eyed prophet says that no man comes\n
 My warehouse eyes, my Arabian drums\n
 Should I leave them by your gate\n
 Or, sad-eyed lady, should I wait?\n

 The kings of Tyrus with their convict list\n
 Are waiting in line for their geranium kiss\n
 And you wouldn’t know it would happen like this\n
 But who among them really wants just to kiss you?\n
 With your childhood flames on your midnight rug\n
 And your Spanish manners and your mother’s drugs\n
 And your cowboy mouth and your curfew plugs\n
 Who among them do you think could resist you?\n
 Sad-eyed lady of the lowlands\n
 Where the sad-eyed prophet says that no man comes\n
 My warehouse eyes, my Arabian drums\n
 Should I leave them by your gate\n
 Or, sad-eyed lady, should I wait?\n

 Oh, the farmers and the businessmen, they all did decide\n
 To show you the dead angels that they used to hide\n
 But why did they pick you to sympathize with their side?\n
 Oh, how could they ever mistake you?\n
 They wished you’d accepted the blame for the farm\n
 But with the sea at your feet and the phony false alarm\n
 And with the child of a hoodlum wrapped up in your arms\n
 How could they ever, ever persuade you?\n
 Sad-eyed lady of the lowlands\n
 Where the sad-eyed prophet says that no man comes\n
 My warehouse eyes, my Arabian drums\n
 Should I leave them by your gate\n
 Or, sad-eyed lady, should I wait?\n

 With your sheet-metal memory of Cannery Row\n
 And your magazine-husband who one day just had to go\n
 And your gentleness now, which you just can’t help but show\n
 Who among them do you think would employ you?\n
 Now you stand with your thief, you’re on his parole\n
 With your holy medallion which your fingertips fold\n
 And your saintlike face and your ghostlike soul\n
 Oh, who among them do you think could destroy you?\n
 Sad-eyed lady of the lowlands\n
 Where the sad-eyed prophet says that no man comes\n
 My warehouse eyes, my Arabian drums\n
 Should I leave them by your gate\n
 Or, sad-eyed lady, should I wait?\n
</string>
 <string name="rainydaywomenlyrics">
  Well, they’ll stone ya when you’re trying to be so good\n
 They’ll stone ya just a-like they said they would\n
 They’ll stone ya when you’re tryin’ to go home\n
 Then they’ll stone ya when you’re there all alone\n
 But I would not feel so all alone\n
 Everybody must get stoned\n

 Well, they’ll stone ya when you’re walkin’ ’long the street\n
 They’ll stone ya when you’re tryin’ to keep your seat\n
 They’ll stone ya when you’re walkin’ on the floor\n
 They’ll stone ya when you’re walkin’ to the door\n
 But I would not feel so all alone\n
 Everybody must get stoned\n

 They’ll stone ya when you’re at the breakfast table\n
 They’ll stone ya when you are young and able\n
 They’ll stone ya when you’re tryin’ to make a buck\n
 They’ll stone ya and then they’ll say, “good luck”\n
 Tell ya what, I would not feel so all alone\n
 Everybody must get stoned\n

 Well, they’ll stone you and say that it’s the end\n
 Then they’ll stone you and then they’ll come back again\n
 They’ll stone you when you’re riding in your car\n
 They’ll stone you when you’re playing your guitar\n
 Yes, but I would not feel so all alone\n
 Everybody must get stoned\n

 Well, they’ll stone you when you walk all alone\n
 They’ll stone you when you are walking home\n
 They’ll stone you and then say you are brave\n
 They’ll stone you when you are set down in your grave\n
 But I would not feel so all alone\n
  Everybody must get stoned\n</string>
 <string name="pledginglyrics">
  Well, early in the mornin’\n
 ’Til late at night\n
 I got a poison headache\n
 But I feel all right\n
 I’m pledging my time to you\n
 Hopin’ you’ll come through, too\n

 Well, the hobo jumped up\n
 He came down natur’lly\n
 After he stole my baby\n
 Then he wanted to steal me\n
 But I’m pledging my time to you\n
 Hopin’ you’ll come through, too\n

 Won’t you come with me, baby?\n
 I’ll take you where you wanna go\n
 And if it don’t work out\n
 You’ll be the first to know\n
 I’m pledging my time to you\n
 Hopin’ you’ll come through, too\n

 Well, the room is so stuffy\n
 I can hardly breathe\n
 Ev’rybody’s gone but me and you\n
 And I can’t be the last to leave\n
 I’m pledging my time to you\n
 Hopin’ you’ll come through, too\n

 Well, they sent for the ambulance\n
 And one was sent\n
 Somebody got lucky\n
 But it was an accident\n
 Now I’m pledging my time to you\n
 Hopin’ you’ll come through, too\n</string>
 <string name="visionsofjohanalyrics">
  Ain’t it just like the night to play tricks \n
  when you’re tryin\' to be so quiet?\n
 We sit here stranded, though we’re all doin’ our best to deny it\n
 And Louise holds a handful of rain, temptin’ you to defy it\n
 Lights flicker from the opposite loft\n
 In this room the heat pipes just cough\n
 The country music station plays soft\n
 But there’s nothing, really nothing to turn off\n
 Just Louise and her lover so entwined\n
 And these visions of Johanna that conquer my mind\n

 In the empty lot where the ladies play \n
  blindman’s bluff with the key chain\n
 And the all-night girls they whisper\n
  of escapades out on the “D” train\n
 We can hear the night watchman click his flashlight\n
 Ask himself if it’s him or them that’s really insane\n
 Louise, she’s all right, she’s just near\n
 She’s delicate and seems like the mirror\n
 But she just makes it all too concise and too clear\n
 That Johanna’s not here\n
 The ghost of ’lectricity howls in the bones of her face\n
 Where these visions of Johanna have now taken my place\n

 Now, little boy lost, he takes himself so seriously\n
 He brags of his misery, he likes to live dangerously\n
 And when bringing her name up\n
 He speaks of a farewell kiss to me\n
 He’s sure got a lotta gall to be so useless and all\n
 Muttering small talk at the wall while I’m in the hall\n
 How can I explain?\n
 Oh, it’s so hard to get on\n
 And these visions of Johanna, they kept me up past the dawn\n

 Inside the museums, Infinity goes up on trial\n
 Voices echo this is what salvation must be like after a while\n
 But Mona Lisa musta had the highway blues\n
 You can tell by the way she smiles\n
 See the primitive wallflower freeze\n
 When the jelly-faced women all sneeze\n
 Hear the one with the mustache say, “Jeeze\n
 I can’t find my knees”\n
 Oh, jewels and binoculars hang from the head of the mule\n
 But these visions of Johanna, they make it all seem so cruel\n

 The peddler now speaks to the countess\n
  who’s pretending to care for him\n
 Sayin’, “Name me someone that’s not a parasite\n
  and I’ll go out and say a prayer for him”\n
 But like Louise always says\n
 “Ya can’t look at much, can ya man?”\n
 As she, herself, prepares for him\n
 And Madonna, she still has not showed\n
 We see this empty cage now corrode\n
 Where her cape of the stage once had flowed\n
 The fiddler, he now steps to the road\n
 He writes ev’rything’s been returned which was owed\n
 On the back of the fish truck that loads\n
 While my conscience explodes\n
 The harmonicas play the skeleton keys and the rain\n
 And these visions of Johanna are now all that remain\n
</string>
 <string name="oneofusmustknowlyrics">
 I didn\'t mean to treat you so bad\n
You shouldn\'t take it so personal\n
I didn\'t mean to make you so sad\n
You just happened to be there, that\'s all\n
When I saw you say goodbye to your friends and smile\n
I thought that it was well understood\n
That you\'d be comin\' back in a little while\n
I didn\'t know that you were sayin\' goodbye for good.\n
But sooner or later one of us must know\n
But you just did what you\'re supposed to do\n
Sooner or later one of us must know\n
That I really did try to get close to you.\n

I couldn\'t see what you could show me\n
Your scarf had kept your mouth well hid\n
I couldn\'t see how you could know me\n
But you said you knew me and I believed you did\n
When you whispered in my ear\n
And asked me if I was leavin\' with you or her\n
I didn\'t realize just what I did hear\n
I didn\'t realize how young you were.\n

But sooner or later one of us must know\n
But you just doing what you\'re supposed to do\n
Sooner or later one of us must know\n
That I really did try to get close to you.\n

I couldn\'t see when it started snowin\'\n
Your voice was all that I heard\n
I couldn\'t see where we were goin\'\n
But you said you knew and I took your word\n
And then you told me later as I apologized\n
That you were just kiddin\' me, you weren\'t really from the farm\n
And I told you, as you clawed out my eyes\n
That I never really meant to do you any harm.\n

But sooner or later one of us must know\n
But you just did what you\'re supposed to do\n
Sooner or later one of us must know\n
That I really did try to get close to you.\n</string>
 <string name="iwantyoulyrics">
  The guilty undertaker sighs\n
 The lonesome organ grinder cries\n
 The silver saxophones say I should refuse you\n
 The cracked bells and washed-out horns\n
 Blow into my face with scorn\n
 But it’s not that way\n
 I wasn’t born to lose you\n

 I want you, I want you\n
 I want you so bad\n
 Honey, I want you\n

 The drunken politician leaps\n
 Upon the street where mothers weep\n
 And the saviors who are fast asleep,\n
  they wait for you\n
 And I wait for them to interrupt\n
 Me drinkin’ from my broken cup\n
 And ask me to\n
 Open up the gate for you\n
 I want you, I want you\n
 I want you so bad\n
 Honey, I want you\n

 How all my fathers, they’ve gone down\n
 True love they’ve been without it\n
 But all their daughters put me down\n
 ’Cause I don’t think about it\n

 Well, I return to the Queen of Spades\n
 And talk with my chambermaid\n
 She knows that I’m not afraid to look at her\n
 She is good to me\n
 And there’s nothing she doesn’t see\n
 She knows where I’d like to be\n
 But it doesn’t matter\n

 I want you, I want you\n
 I want you so bad\n
 Honey, I want you\n

 Now your dancing child with his Chinese suit\n
 He spoke to me, I took his flute\n
 No, I wasn’t very cute to him, was I?\n
 But I did it, though, because he lied\n
 Because he took you for a ride\n
 And because time was on his side\n
 And because I . . .\n

 I want you, I want you\n
 I want you so bad\n
 Honey, I want you\n
 </string>
 <string name="stuckinsidelyrics">
  Oh, the ragman draws circles\n
 Up and down the block\n
 I’d ask him what the matter was\n
 But I know that he don’t talk\n
 And the ladies treat me kindly\n
 And furnish me with tape\n
 But deep inside my heart\n
 I know I can’t escape\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Well, Shakespeare, he’s in the alley\n
 With his pointed shoes and his bells\n
 Speaking to some French girl\n
 Who says she knows me well\n
 And I would send a message\n
 To find out if she’s talked\n
 But the post office has been stolen\n
 And the mailbox is locked\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Mona tried to tell me\n
 To stay away from the train line\n
 She said that all the railroad men\n
 Just drink up your blood like wine\n
 An’ I said, “Oh, I didn’t know that\n
 But then again, there’s only one I’ve met\n
 An’ he just smoked my eyelids\n
 An’ punched my cigarette”\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Grandpa died last week\n
 And now he’s buried in the rocks\n
 But everybody still talks about\n
 How badly they were shocked\n
 But me, I expected it to happen\n
 I knew he’d lost control\n
 When he built a fire on Main Street\n
 And shot it full of holes\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Now the senator came down here\n
 Showing ev’ryone his gun\n
 Handing out free tickets\n
 To the wedding of his son\n
 An’ me, I nearly got busted\n
 An’ wouldn’t it be my luck\n
 To get caught without a ticket\n
 And be discovered beneath a truck\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Now the preacher looked so baffled\n
 When I asked him why he dressed\n
 With twenty pounds of headlines\n
 Stapled to his chest\n
 But he cursed me when I proved it to him\n
 Then I whispered, “Not even you can hide\n
 You see, you’re just like me\n
 I hope you’re satisfied”\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Now the rainman gave me two cures\n
 Then he said, “Jump right in”\n
 The one was Texas medicine\n
 The other was just railroad gin\n
 An’ like a fool I mixed them\n
 An’ it strangled up my mind\n
 An’ now people just get uglier\n
 An’ I have no sense of time\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 When Ruthie says come see her\n
 In her honky-tonk lagoon\n
 Where I can watch her waltz for free\n
 ’Neath her Panamanian moon\n
 An’ I say, “Aw come on now\n
 You must know about my debutante”\n
 An’ she says, “Your debutante just knows what you need\n
 But I know what you want”\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n

 Now the bricks lay on Grand Street\n
 Where the neon madmen climb\n
 They all fall there so perfectly\n
 It all seems so well timed\n
 An’ here I sit so patiently\n
 Waiting to find out what price\n
 You have to pay to get out of\n
 Going through all these things twice\n
 Oh, Mama, can this really be the end\n
 To be stuck inside of Mobile\n
 With the Memphis blues again\n</string>
 <string name="leopardskinlyrics">
  Well, I see you got your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n
 Yes, I see you got your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n
 Well, you must tell me, baby\n
 How your head feels under somethin’ like that\n
 Under your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n

 Well, you look so pretty in it\n
 Honey, can I jump on it sometime?\n
 Yes, I just wanna see\n
 If it’s really that expensive kind\n
 You know it balances on your head\n
 Just like a mattress balances\n
 On a bottle of wine\n
 Your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n

 Well, if you wanna see the sun rise\n
 Honey, I know where\n
 We’ll go out and see it sometime\n
 We’ll both just sit there and stare\n
 Me with my belt\n
 Wrapped around my head\n
 And you just sittin’ there\n
 In your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n

 Well, I asked the doctor if I could see you\n
 It’s bad for your health, he said\n
 Yes, I disobeyed his orders\n
 I came to see you\n
 But I found him there instead\n
  You know, I don’t mind him cheatin’ on me\n
 But I sure wish he’d take that off his head\n
 Your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n

 Well, I see you got a new boyfriend\n
 You know, I never seen him before\n
 Well, I saw him\n
 Makin’ love to you\n
 You forgot to close the garage door\n
 You might think he loves you for your money\n
 But I know what he really loves you for\n
 It’s your brand new leopard-skin pill-box hat\n
 </string>
 <string name="justlikeawomenlyrics">Nobody feels any pain\n
 Tonight as I stand inside the rain\n
 Ev’rybody knows\n
 That Baby’s got new clothes\n
 But lately I see her ribbons and her bows\n
 Have fallen from her curls\n
 She takes just like a woman, yes, she does\n
 She makes love just like a woman, yes, she does\n
 And she aches just like a woman\n
 But she breaks just like a little girl\n

 Queen Mary, she’s my friend\n
 Yes, I believe I’ll go see her again\n
 Nobody has to guess\n
 That Baby can’t be blessed\n
 Till she sees finally that she’s like all the rest\n
 With her fog, her amphetamine and her pearls\n
 She takes just like a woman, yes, she does\n
 She makes love just like a woman, yes, she does\n
 And she aches just like a woman\n
 But she breaks just like a little girl\n

 It was raining from the first\n
 And I was dying there of thirst\n
 So I came in here\n
 And your long-time curse hurts\n
 But what’s worse\n
 Is this pain in here\n
 I can’t stay in here\n
 Ain’t it clear that—\n

 I just can’t fit\n
 Yes, I believe it’s time for us to quit\n
 When we meet again\n
 Introduced as friends\n
 Please don’t let on that you knew me when\n
 I was hungry and it was your world\n
 Ah, you fake just like a woman, yes, you do\n
 You make love just like a woman, yes, you do\n
 Then you ache just like a woman\n
 But you break just like a little girl\n
</string>
 <string name="mostlikelyllyrics">You say you love me\n
 And you’re thinkin’ of me\n
 But you know you could be wrong\n
 You say you told me\n
 That you wanna hold me\n
 But you know you’re not that strong\n
 I just can’t do what I done before\n
 I just can’t beg you anymore\n
 I’m gonna let you pass\n
 And I’ll go last\n
 Then time will tell just who fell\n
 And who’s been left behind\n
 When you go your way and I go mine\n

 You say you disturb me\n
 And you don’t deserve me\n
 But you know sometimes you lie\n
 You say you’re shakin’\n
 And you’re always achin’\n
 But you know how hard you try\n
 Sometimes it gets so hard to care\n
 It can’t be this way ev’rywhere\n
 And I’m gonna let you pass\n
 Yes, and I’ll go last\n
 Then time will tell just who fell\n
 And who’s been left behind\n
 When you go your way and I go mine\n

 The judge, he holds a grudge\n
 He’s gonna call on you\n
 But he’s badly built\n
 And he walks on stilts\n
 Watch out he don’t fall on you\n

 You say you’re sorry\n
 For tellin’ stories\n
 That you know I believe are true\n
 You say ya got some\n
 Other kinda lover\n
 And yes, I believe you do\n
 You say my kisses are not like his\n
 But this time I’m not gonna tell you why that is\n
 I’m just gonna let you pass\n
 Yes, and I’ll go last\n
 Then time will tell who fell\n
 And who’s been left behind\n
 When you go your way and I go mine\n</string>
 <string name="temporarylikeachileslyrics">
  Standing on your window, honey\n
 Yes, I’ve been here before\n
 Feeling so harmless\n
 I’m looking at your second door\n
 How come you don’t send me no regards?\n
 You know I want your lovin’\n
 Honey, why are you so hard?\n

 Kneeling ’neath your ceiling\n
 Yes, I guess I’ll be here for a while\n
 I’m tryin’ to read your portrait, but\n
 I’m helpless, like a rich man’s child\n
 How come you send someone out to have me barred?\n
 You know I want your lovin’\n
 Honey, why are you so hard?\n

 Like a poor fool in his prime\n
 Yes, I know you can hear me walk\n
 But is your heart made out of stone, or is it lime\n
 Or is it just solid rock?\n

 Well, I rush into your hallway\n
 Lean against your velvet door\n
 I watch upon your scorpion\n
 Who crawls across your circus floor\n
 Just what do you think you have to guard?\n
 You know I want your lovin’\n
 Honey, but you’re so hard\n

 Achilles is in your alleyway\n
 He don’t want me here, he does brag\n
 He’s pointing to the sky\n
 And he’s hungry, like a man in drag\n
 How come you get someone like him to be your guard?\n
 You know I want your lovin’\n
 Honey, but you’re so hard\n</string>
 <string name="absolutelysweetlyrics">
  Well, your railroad gate, you know I just can’t jump it\n
 Sometimes it gets so hard, you see\n
 I’m just sitting here beating on my trumpet\n
 With all these promises you left for me\n
 But where are you tonight, sweet Marie?\n

 Well, I waited for you when I was half sick\n
 Yes, I waited for you when you hated me\n
 Well, I waited for you inside of the frozen traffic\n
 When you knew I had some other place to be\n
 Now, where are you tonight, sweet Marie?\n

 Well, anybody can be just like me, obviously\n
 But then, now again, not too many can be like you, fortunately\n

 Well, six white horses that you did promise\n
 Were fin’lly delivered down to the penitentiary\n
 But to live outside the law, you must be honest\n
 I know you always say that you agree\n
 But where are you tonight, sweet Marie?\n

 Well, I don’t know how it happened\n
 But the riverboat captain, he knows my fate\n
 But ev’rybody else, even yourself\n
 They’re just gonna have to wait\n

 Well, I got the fever down in my pockets\n
 The Persian drunkard, he follows me\n
 Yes, I can take him to your house but I can’t unlock it\n
 You see, you forgot to leave me with the key\n
 Oh, where are you tonight, sweet Marie?\n

 Now, I been in jail when all my mail showed\n
 That a man can’t give his address out to bad company\n
 And now I stand here lookin’ at your yellow railroad\n
 In the ruins of your balcony\n
 Wond’ring where you are tonight, sweet Marie\n</string>
 <string name="fourthtimearoundlyrics">
  When she said\n
 “Don’t waste your words, they’re just lies”\n
 I cried she was deaf\n
 And she worked on my face until breaking my eyes\n
 Then said, “What else you got left?”\n
 It was then that I got up to leave\n
 But she said, “Don’t forget\n
 Everybody must give something back\n
 For something they get”\n

 I stood there and hummed\n
 I tapped on her drum and asked her how come\n
 And she buttoned her boot\n
 And straightened her suit\n
 Then she said, “Don’t get cute”\n
 So I forced my hands in my pockets\n
 And felt with my thumbs\n
 And gallantly handed her\n
 My very last piece of gum\n

 She threw me outside\n
 I stood in the dirt where ev’ryone walked\n
 And after finding I’d\n
 Forgotten my shirt\n
 I went back and knocked\n
 I waited in the hallway, she went to get it\n
 And I tried to make sense\n
 Out of that picture of you in your wheelchair\n
 That leaned up against . . .\n

 Her Jamaican rum\n
 And when she did come, I asked her for some\n
 She said, “No, dear”\n
 I said, “Your words aren’t clear\n
 You’d better spit out your gum”\n
 She screamed till her face got so red\n
 Then she fell on the floor\n
 And I covered her up and then\n
 Thought I’d go look through her drawer\n

 And when I was through\n
 I filled up my shoe\n
 And brought it to you\n
 And you, you took me in\n
 You loved me then\n
 You didn’t waste time\n
 And I, I never took much\n
 I never asked for your crutch\n
 Now don’t ask for mine\n</string>

 <string name="obviouslyfivebelieverlyrics">
  Early in the mornin’\n
 Early in the mornin’\n
 I’m callin’ you to\n
 I’m callin’ you to\n
 Please come home\n
 Yes, I guess I could make it without you\n
 If I just didn’t feel so all alone\n

 Don’t let me down\n
 Don’t let me down\n
 I won’t let you down\n
 I won’t let you down\n
 No I won’t\n
 You know I can if you can, honey\n
 But, honey, please don’t\n

 I got my black dog barkin’\n
 Black dog barkin’\n
 Yes it is now\n
 Yes it is now\n
 Outside my yard\n
 Yes, I could tell you what he means\n
 If I just didn’t have to try so hard\n

 Your mama’s workin’\n
 Your mama’s moanin’\n
 She’s cryin’ you know\n
 She’s tryin’ you know\n
 You better go now\n
 Well, I’d tell you what she wants\n
 But I just don’t know how\n

 Fifteen jugglers\n
 Fifteen jugglers\n
 Five believers\n
 Five believers\n
 All dressed like men\n
 Tell yo’ mama not to worry because\n
 They’re just my friends\n

 Early in the mornin’\n
 Early in the mornin’\n
 I’m callin’ you to\n
 I’m callin’ you to\n
 Please come home\n
 Yes, I could make it without you\n
 If I just did not feel so all alone\n</string>


</resources>