<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="youarenogoodlyrics">
        Well I don\'t know why I love you like I do\n
 Nobody in the world can get along with you.\n
 You got the ways of a devil sleeping in a lion\'s den\n
 I come home last night you wouldn\'t even let me in.\n

 Well sometimes you\'re as sweet as anybody want to be\n
 When you get a crazy notion of jumpin\' all over me\n
 Well you give me the blues I guess you\'re satisfied\n
 An\' you give me the blues I wanna lay down and die.\n

 I helped you when you had no shoes on your feet, pretty mama\n
 I helped you when you had no food to eat.\n
 You\'re the kind of woman I just don\'t understand\n
 You\'re takin\' all my money and give it to another man.\n

 Well you\'re the kinda woman makes a man lose his brain\n
 You\'re the kinda woman drives a man insane\n
 You give me the blues, I guess you\'re satisfied\n
 You give me the blues, I wanna lay down and die\n

 Well you give me the blues, I wanna lay down and die\n


    </string>
    <string name="inmytimeofdyinglyrics">
    Well, in my time of dying don\'t want nobody to mourn\n
 All I want for you to do is take my body home\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Well, well, well\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Jesus gonna make up, Jesus gonna make up\n
 Jesus gonna make up my dying bed\n

 Well, meet me Jesus, meet me, meet me\n
 in the middle of the air\n
 If these wings should fail to me\n
 Lord, won\'t you meet me with another pair\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Well, well, well\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Jesus gonna make up, Jesus gonna make up\n
 Jesus gonna make up my dying bed\n

 Lord, in my time of dying don\'t want nobody to cry\n
 All I want you to do is take me when I die\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Well, well, well\n
 Well, well, well, so I can die easy\n
 Jesus gonna make up, Jesus gonna make up\n
 Jesus gonna make up my dying bed\n

</string>
    <string name="manofconstantsorrowlyrics">
        I am a man of constant sorrow\n
 I\'ve seen trouble all my days\n
 I\'ll say goodbye to Colorado\n
 Where I was born and partly raised\n

 Through this open world I\'m a-bound to ramble\n
 Through ice and snow, sleet and rain\n
 Im a-bound to ride that mornin\' railroad\n
 Perhaps I\'ll die upon that train\n

 Your mother says that I\'m a stranger\n
 A face you\'ll never see no more\n
 But here\'s one promise to ya\n
 I\'ll see you on God\'s golden shore\n

 I\'m a-goin\' back to Colorado\n
 The place that I\'ve started from\n
 If I\'d knowed how bad you\'d treat me\n
 Babe, I never would have come\n

    </string>
<string name="fixingtodielyrics">
 Feeling funny in my mind, Lord,\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die, fixing to die\n
 Feeling funny in my mind, Lord\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die\n
 Well, I don\'t mind dying\n
 But I hate to leave my children crying\n
 Well, I look over yonder to that burying ground\n
 Look over yonder to that burying ground\n
 Sure seems lonesome, Lord, when the sun goes down\n

 Feeling funny in my eyes, Lord,\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die, fixing to die\n
 Feeling funny in my eyes, Lord\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die\n
 Well, I don\'t mind dying but\n
 I hate to leave my children crying\n
 There\'s a black smoke rising, Lord\n
 It\'s rising up above my head, up above my head\n
 It\'s rising up above my head, up above my head\n
 And tell Jesus make up my dying bed.\n

 I\'m walking kind of funny, Lord\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die, fixing to die\n
 Yes I\'m walking kind of funny, Lord\n
 I believe I\'m fixing to die\n
 Fixing to die, fixing to die\n
 Well, I don\'t mind dying\n
 But I hate to leave my children crying.\n

</string>
    <string name="prettypeggylyrics">
I\'ve been around this whole country \n
 But I never yet found Fenneario\n

 Well, as we marched down, as we marched down\n
 Well, as we marched down to Fennerio\'\n
 Well, our captain fell in love with a lady like a dove\n
 Her name that she had was Pretty Peggy-O\n

 Well, what will your mother say, what will your mother say\n
 What will your mother say, Pretty Peggy-O\n
 What will your mother say to know you\'re going away\n
 You\'re never, never, never coming back-io ?\n

 Come a-running down your stairs \n
 Come a-running down your stairs\n
 Come a-running down your stairs, Pretty Peggy-O\n
 Come a-running down your stairs \n
 Combing back your yellow hair\n
 You\'re the prettiest darned girl I ever seen-io.\n

 The lieutenant he has gone \n
 The lieutenant he has gone\n
 The lieutenant he has gone, Pretty Peggy-O\n
 The lieutenant he has gone, long gone\n
 He\'s a-riding down in Texas with the rodeo.\n

 Well, our captain he is dead, our captain he is dead\n
 Our captain he is dead, Pretty Peggy-O\n
 Well, our captain he is dead, died for a maid\n
 He\'s buried somewhere in Louisiana-O.\n


    </string>
    <string name="highway51lyrics" >
        Highway 51 runs right by my baby\'s door\n
 Highway 51 runs right by my baby\'s door\n
 If I don\'t get the girl I\'m loving\n
 Won\'t go down to Highway 51 no more.\n

 Well, I know that highway like I know my hand\n
 Yes, I know that highway like I know the back of my hand\n
 Running from up Wisconsin way down to no man\'s land.\n

 Well, if I should die before my time should come\n
 And if I should die before my time should come\n
 Won\'t you bury my body out on the Highway 51.\n

 Highway 51 runs right by my baby\'s door\n
 I said, Highway 51 runs right by my baby\'s door\n
 If I don\'t get the girl I\'m loving\n
 Won\'t go down to Highway 51 no more.\n
    </string>
    <string name="gospelplowlyrics">
     Mary wore three links of chain \n
 Every link was Jesus name\n
 Keep your hand on that plow, hold on\n
 Oh Lord, Oh Lord, keep your hand on that plow, hold on.\n
 Mary, Mark, Luke and John\n
 All these prophets so good and gone\n
 Keep your hand on that plow, hold on\n
 Oh Lord, Oh Lord, keep your hand on that plow, hold on.\n
 Well, I never been to heaven\n
 But I\'ve been told streets up there\n
 Are lined with gold\n
 Keep your hand on that plow, hold on\n
 Oh Lord, Oh Lord, keep your hand on that plow, hold on.\n
 Oh Lord, Oh Lord, keep your hand on that plow, hold on.\n
 Oh Lord, Oh Lord, keep your hand on that plow, hold on.\n
    </string>

    <string name="babyletmefollowyoulyrics">
     I first heard this from Ric von Schmidt. He lives in Cambridge.\n
 Ric is a blues guitarplayer. I met him one day on \n
 The green pastures of the Harvard University. \n

 Baby let me follow you down, baby let me follow you down\n
 Well I\'ll do anything in this godalmighty world\n
 If you just let me follow you down.\n

 Can I come home with you, baby can I come home with you ?\n
 Yes I\'ll do anything in this godalmighty world\n
 If you just let me come home with you.\n

 Baby let me follow you down, baby let me follow you down\n
 Well I\'ll do anything in this godalmighty world\n
 If you just let me follow you down.\n

 Yes I\'ll do anything in this godalmighty world\n
 If you just let me follow you down.\n

    </string>
    <string name="houseofrisingsunlyrics">
     There is a house down in New Orleans they call the rising sun\n
 And it\'s been the ruin of many a poor girl and me, oh God, I\'m one.\n

 My mother was a tailor, she sowed these new blue jeans\n
 My sweetheart was a gambler, Lord, down in New Orleans.\n

 Now the only thing a gambler needs is a suitcase and a trunk\n
 And the only time when he\'s satisfied is when he\'s on a drunk.\n

 He fills his glasses up to the brim and he\'ll pass the cards around\n
 And the only pleasure he gets out of life is rambling from town to town\n

 Oh tell my baby sister not to do what I have done\n
 But shun that house in New Orleans they call the rising sun.\n

 Well with one foot on the platform and the other foot on the train\n
 I\'m going back to New Orleans to wear that ball and chain.\n

 I\'m going back to New Orleans, my race is almost run\n
 I\'m going back to end my life down in the rising sun.\n

 There is a house in New Orleans they call the rising sun\n
 And it\'s been the ruin of many a poor girl and me, oh God, I\'m one.\n

    </string>
    <string name="freighttrainblueslyrics">
     I was born in Dixie in a boomer shed\n
 Just a little shanty by the railroad track\n
 Freight train was it taught me how to cry\n
 The holler of the driver was my lullaby\n
 I got the freight train blues\n
 Oh Lord mama, I got them in the bottom of my rambling shoes\n
 And when the whistle blows I gotta go baby, don\'t you know\n
 Well, it looks like I\'m never gonna lose the freight train blues.\n

 Well, my daddy was a fireman and my mama-ha\n
 She was the only daughter of an engineer\n
 My sweetheart was a brakeman and it ain\'t no joke\n
 Seems a waste to get a good man broke\n
 I got the freight train blues\n
 Oh Lord mama, I got them in the bottom of my rambling shoes\n
 And when the whistle blows I gotta go mama, don\'t you know\n
 Well, it looks like I\'m never gonna lose the freight train blues.\n

 Well, the only thing that makes me laugh again\n
 Is a southbound whistle on a southbound train\n
 Every place I wanna go I never can go\n
 Because you know I got the freight train blues\n
 Oh Lord mama, I got them in the bottom of my rambling shoes.\n


    </string>


    <string name="songtowoodylyrics">
     I’m out here a thousand miles from my home\n
 Walkin’ a road other men have gone down\n
 I’m seein’ your world of people and things\n
 Your paupers and peasants and princes and kings\n

 Hey, hey, Woody Guthrie, I wrote you a song\n
 ’Bout a funny ol’ world that’s a-comin’ along\n
 Seems sick an’ it’s hungry, it’s tired an’ it’s torn\n
 It looks like it’s a-dyin’ an’ it’s hardly been born\n

 Hey, Woody Guthrie, but I know that you know\n
 All the things that I’m a-sayin’ an’ a-many times more\n
 I’m a-singin’ you the song, but I can’t sing enough\n
 ’Cause there’s not many men that done the things that you’ve done\n

 Here’s to Cisco an’ Sonny an’ Leadbelly too\n
 An’ to all the good people that traveled with you\n
 Here’s to the hearts and the hands of the men\n
 That come with the dust and are gone with the wind\n

 I’m a-leavin’ tomorrow, but I could leave today\n
 Somewhere down the road someday\n
 The very last thing that I’d want to do\n
 Is to say I’ve been hittin’ some hard travelin’ too\n

    </string>
    <string name="seethatmygraveiskeptcleanlyrics">
     Well there\'s one kind of favor I\'ll ask for you \n
 Well there\'s one kind of favor I\'ll ask for you \n
 There\'s just one kind of favor I\'ll ask for you\n
 You can see that my grave is kept clean. \n

 And there\'s two white horses following me \n
 And there\'s two white horses following me \n
 I got two white horses following me\n
 Waiting on my burying ground.\n

 Did you ever hear that coffin sound\n
 Did you ever hear that coffin sound\n
 Did you ever hear that coffin sound\n
 Means another poor boy is underground.\n

 Did you ever hear them church bells toll\n
 Did you ever hear them church bells toll \n
 Did you ever hear them church bells toll \n
 Means another poor boy is dead and gone. \n

 And my heart stopped beating and my hands turned cold\n
 And my heart stopped beating and my hands turned cold \n
 And my heart stopped beating and my hands turned cold \n
 Now I believe what the Bible told.\n

 There\'s just one last favor I\'ll ask for you \n
 And there\'s one last favor I\'ll ask for you \n
 There\'s just one last favor I\'ll ask for you \n
 See that my grave is kept clean.\n


    </string>




</resources>