<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="blowininthewindlyrics">
        How many roads must a man walk down\n
 Before you call him a man?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many seas must a white dove sail\n
 Before she sleeps in the sand?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many times must the cannonballs fly\n
 Before they’re forever banned?\n
 The answer, my friend, is blowin’ in the wind\n
 The answer is blowin’ in the wind\n

 How many years can a mountain exist\n
 Before it’s washed to the sea?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many years can some people exist\n
 Before they’re allowed to be free?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many times can a man turn his head\n
 Pretending he just doesn’t see?\n
 The answer, my friend, is blowin’ in the wind\n
 The answer is blowin’ in the wind\n

 How many times must a man look up\n
 Before he can see the sky?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many ears must one man have\n
 Before he can hear people cry?\n
 Yes, ’n’ how many deaths will it take till he knows\n
 That too many people have died?\n
 The answer, my friend, is blowin’ in the wind\n
 The answer is blowin’ in the wind\n

    </string>
    <string name="girlfromthenorthcountrylyrics">
        Well, if you’re travelin’ in the north country fair\n
 Where the winds hit heavy on the borderline\n
 Remember me to one who lives there\n
 She once was a true love of mine\n

 Well, if you go when the snowflakes storm\n
 When the rivers freeze and summer ends\n
 Please see if she’s wearing a coat so warm\n
 To keep her from the howlin’ winds\n

 Please see for me if her hair hangs long,\n
 If it rolls and flows all down her breast.\n
 Please see for me if her hair hangs long,\n
 That’s the way I remember her best.\n

 I’m a-wonderin’ if she remembers me at all\n
 Many times I’ve often prayed\n
 In the darkness of my night\n
 In the brightness of my day\n

 So if you’re travelin’ in the north country fair\n
 Where the winds hit heavy on the borderline\n
 Remember me to one who lives there\n
 She once was a true love of mine\n
    </string>
    <string name="mastersofwarlyrics">
        Come you masters of war\n
 You that build all the guns\n
 You that build the death planes\n
 You that build the big bombs\n
 You that hide behind walls\n
 You that hide behind desks\n
 I just want you to know\n
 I can see through your masks\n

 You that never done nothin’\n
 But build to destroy\n
 You play with my world\n
 Like it’s your little toy\n
 You put a gun in my hand\n
 And you hide from my eyes\n
 And you turn and run farther\n
 When the fast bullets fly\n

 Like Judas of old\n
 You lie and deceive\n
 A world war can be won\n
 You want me to believe\n
 But I see through your eyes\n
 And I see through your brain\n
 Like I see through the water\n
 That runs down my drain\n

 You fasten the triggers\n
 For the others to fire\n
 Then you set back and watch\n
 When the death count gets higher\n
 You hide in your mansion\n
 As young people’s blood\n
 Flows out of their bodies\n
 And is buried in the mud\n

 You’ve thrown the worst fear\n
 That can ever be hurled\n
 Fear to bring children\n
 Into the world\n
 For threatening my baby\n
 Unborn and unnamed\n
 You ain’t worth the blood\n
 That runs in your veins\n

 How much do I know\n
 To talk out of turn\n
 You might say that I’m young\n
 You might say I’m unlearned\n
 But there’s one thing I know\n
 Though I’m younger than you\n
 Even Jesus would never\n
 Forgive what you do\n

 Let me ask you one question\n
 Is your money that good\n
 Will it buy you forgiveness\n
 Do you think that it could\n
 I think you will find\n
 When your death takes its toll\n
 All the money you made\n
 Will never buy back your soul\n

 And I hope that you die\n
 And your death’ll come soon\n
 I will follow your casket\n
 In the pale afternoon\n
 And I’ll watch while you’re lowered\n
 Down to your deathbed\n
 And I’ll stand o’er your grave\n
 ’Til I’m sure that you’re dead\n

    </string>
    <string name="downthehighwaylyrics">
        Well, I’m walkin’ down the highway\n
 With my suitcase in my hand\n
 Yes, I’m walkin’ down the highway\n
 With my suitcase in my hand\n
 Lord, I really miss my baby\n
 She’s in some far-off land\n

 Well, your streets are gettin’ empty\n
 Lord, your highway’s gettin’ filled\n
 And your streets are gettin’ empty\n
 And your highway’s gettin’ filled\n
 Well, the way I love that woman\n
 I swear it’s bound to get me killed\n

 Well, I been gamblin’ so long\n
 Lord, I ain’t got much more to lose\n
 Yes, I been gamblin’ so long\n
 Lord, I ain’t got much more to lose\n
 Right now I’m havin’ trouble\n
 Please don’t take away my highway shoes\n

 Well, I’m bound to get lucky, baby\n
 Or I’m bound to die tryin’\n
 Yes, I’m a-bound to get lucky, baby\n
 Lord, Lord I’m a-bound to die tryin’\n
 Well, meet me in the middle of the ocean\n
 And we’ll leave this ol’ highway behind\n

 Well, the ocean took my baby\n
 My baby stole my heart from me\n
 Yes, the ocean took my baby\n
 My baby took my heart from me\n
 She packed it all up in a suitcase\n
 Lord, she took it away to Italy, Italy\n

 So, I’m a-walkin’ down your highway\n
 Just as far as my poor eyes can see\n
 Yes, I’m a-walkin’ down your highway\n
 Just as far as my eyes can see\n
 From the Golden Gate Bridge\n
 All the way to the Statue of Liberty\n

    </string>
    <string name="bobdylansbluelyrics">
        Well, the Lone Ranger and Tonto\n
 They are ridin’ down the line\n
 Fixin’ ev’rybody’s troubles\n
 Ev’rybody’s ’cept mine\n
 Somebody musta tol’ ’em\n
 That I was doin’ fine\n

 Oh you five and ten cent women\n
 With nothin’ in your heads\n
 I got a real gal I’m lovin’\n
 And Lord I’ll love her till I’m dead\n
 Go away from my door and my window too\n
 Right now\n

 Lord, I ain’t goin’ down to no race track\n
 See no sports car run\n
 I don’t have no sports car\n
 And I don’t even care to have one\n
 I can walk anytime around the block\n

 Well, the wind keeps a-blowin’ me\n
 Up and down the street\n
 With my hat in my hand\n
 And my boots on my feet\n
 Watch out so you don’t step on me\n

 Well, lookit here buddy\n
 You want to be like me\n
 Pull out your six-shooter\n
 And rob every bank you can see\n
 Tell the judge I said it was all right\n
 Yes!\n

    </string>
    <string name="ahardrainsgonnafalllyrics">
      Oh, where have you been, my blue-eyed son?\n
 Oh, where have you been, my darling young one?\n
 I’ve stumbled on the side of twelve misty mountains\n
 I’ve walked and I’ve crawled on six crooked highways\n
 I’ve stepped in the middle of seven sad forests\n
 I’ve been out in front of a dozen dead oceans\n
 I’ve been ten thousand miles in the mouth of a graveyard\n
 And it’s a hard, and it’s a hard, it’s a hard, and it’s a hard\n
 And it’s a hard rain’s a-gonna fall\n

 Oh, what did you see, my blue-eyed son?\n
 Oh, what did you see, my darling young one?\n
 I saw a newborn baby with wild wolves all around it\n
 I saw a highway of diamonds with nobody on it\n
 I saw a black branch with blood that kept drippin’\n
 I saw a room full of men with their hammers a-bleedin’\n
 I saw a white ladder all covered with water\n
 I saw ten thousand talkers whose tongues were all broken\n
 I saw guns and sharp swords in the hands of young children\n
 And it’s a hard, and it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard\n
 And it’s a hard rain’s a-gonna fall\n

 And what did you hear, my blue-eyed son?\n
 And what did you hear, my darling young one?\n
 I heard the sound of a thunder, it roared out a warnin’\n
 Heard the roar of a wave that could drown the whole world\n
 Heard one hundred drummers whose hands were a-blazin’\n
 Heard ten thousand whisperin’ and nobody listenin’\n
 Heard one person starve, I heard many people laughin’\n
 Heard the song of a poet who died in the gutter\n
 Heard the sound of a clown who cried in the alley\n
 And it’s a hard, and it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard\n
 And it’s a hard rain’s a-gonna fall\n

 Oh, who did you meet, my blue-eyed son?\n
 Who did you meet, my darling young one?\n
 I met a young child beside a dead pony\n
 I met a white man who walked a black dog\n
 I met a young woman whose body was burning\n
 I met a young girl, she gave me a rainbow\n
 I met one man who was wounded in love\n
 I met another man who was wounded with hatred\n
 And it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard\n
 It’s a hard rain’s a-gonna fall\n

 Oh, what’ll you do now, my blue-eyed son?\n
 Oh, what’ll you do now, my darling young one?\n
 I’m a-goin’ back out ’fore the rain starts a-fallin’\n
 I’ll walk to the depths of the deepest black forest\n
 Where the people are many and their hands are all empty\n
 Where the pellets of poison are flooding their waters\n
 Where the home in the valley meets the damp dirty prison\n
 Where the executioner’s face is always well hidden\n
 Where hunger is ugly, where souls are forgotten\n
 Where black is the color, where none is the number\n
 And I’ll tell it and think it and speak it and breathe it\n
 And reflect it from the mountain so all souls can see it\n
 Then I’ll stand on the ocean until I start sinkin’\n
 But I’ll know my song well before I start singin’\n
 And it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard, it’s a hard\n
 It’s a hard rain’s a-gonna fall\n

    </string>
    <string name="dontthinktwicelyrics">
        It ain’t no use to sit and wonder why, babe\n
 It don’t matter, anyhow\n
 An’ it ain’t no use to sit and wonder why, babe\n
 If you don’t know by now\n
 When your rooster crows at the break of dawn\n
 Look out your window and I’ll be gone\n
 You’re the reason I’m trav’lin’ on\n
 Don’t think twice, it’s all right\n

 It ain’t no use in turnin’ on your light, babe\n
 That light I never knowed\n
 An’ it ain’t no use in turnin’ on your light, babe\n
 I’m on the dark side of the road\n
 Still I wish there was somethin’ you would do or say\n
 To try and make me change my mind and stay\n
 We never did too much talkin’ anyway\n
 So don’t think twice, it’s all right\n

 It ain’t no use in callin’ out my name, gal\n
 Like you never did before\n
 It ain’t no use in callin’ out my name, gal\n
 I can’t hear you anymore\n
 I’m a-thinkin’ and a-wond’rin’ all the way down the road\n
 I once loved a woman, a child I’m told\n
 I give her my heart but she wanted my soul\n
 But don’t think twice, it’s all right\n

 I’m walkin’ down that long, lonesome road, babe\n
 Where I’m bound, I can’t tell\n
 But goodbye’s too good a word, gal\n
 So I’ll just say fare thee well\n
 I ain’t sayin’ you treated me unkind\n
 You could have done better but I don’t mind\n
 You just kinda wasted my precious time\n
 But don’t think twice, it’s all right\n

    </string>
    <string name="bobdylansdreamfreewheelinglyrics">
        While riding on a train goin’ west\n
 I fell asleep for to take my rest\n
 I dreamed a dream that made me sad\n
 Concerning myself and the first few friends I had\n

 With half-damp eyes I stared to the room\n
 Where my friends and I spent many an afternoon\n
 Where we together weathered many a storm\n
 Laughin’ and singin’ till the \n
     early hours of the morn\n

 By the old wooden stove where our hats was hung\n
 Our words were told, our songs were sung\n
 Where we longed for nothin’\n
     and were quite satisfied\n
 Talkin’ and a-jokin’ about the world outside\n

 With haunted hearts through the heat and cold\n
 We never thought we could ever get old\n
 We thought we could sit forever in fun\n
 But our chances really was a million to one\n

 As easy it was to tell black from white\n
 It was all that easy to tell wrong from right\n
 And our choices were few \n
     and the thought never hit\n
 That the one road we traveled \n
     would ever shatter and split\n

 How many a year has passed and gone\n
 And many a gamble has been lost and won\n
 And many a road taken by many a friend\n
 And each one I’ve never seen again\n

 I wish, I wish, I wish in vain\n
 That we could sit simply in that room again\n
 Ten thousand dollars at the drop of a hat\n
 I’d give it all gladly if our lives could be like that\n

    </string>
    <string name="oxfordtownlyrics">
        Oxford Town, Oxford Town\n
 Ev’rybody’s got their heads bowed down\n
 The sun don’t shine above the ground\n
 Ain’t a-goin’ down to Oxford Town\n

 He went down to Oxford Town\n
 Guns and clubs followed him down\n
 All because his face was brown\n
 Better get away from Oxford Town\n

 Oxford Town around the bend\n
 He come in to the door, he couldn’t get in\n
 All because of the color of his skin\n
 What do you think about that, my frien’?\n

 Me and my gal, my gal’s son\n
        We got met with a tear gas bomb\n
 I don’t even know why we come\n
 Goin’ back where we come from\n

 Oxford Town in the afternoon\n
 Ev’rybody singin’ a sorrowful tune\n
 Two men died ’neath the Mississippi moon\n
 Somebody better investigate soon\n

 Oxford Town, Oxford Town\n
 Ev’rybody’s got their heads bowed down\n
 The sun don’t shine above the ground\n
 Ain’t a-goin’ down to Oxford Town\n

    </string>
    <string name="talkinworldwar3lyrics">
Some time ago a crazy dream came to me\n
 I dreamt I was walkin’ into World War Three\n
 I went to the doctor the very next day\n
 To see what kinda words he could say\n
 He said it was a bad dream\n
 I wouldn’t worry ’bout it none, though\n
 They were my own dreams and they’re only in my head\n

 I said, “Hold it, Doc, a World War passed through my brain”\n
 He said, “Nurse, get your pad, this boy’s insane”\n
 He grabbed my arm, I said, “Ouch!”\n
 As I landed on the psychiatric couch\n
 He said, “Tell me about it”\n

 Well, the whole thing started at 3 o’clock fast\n
 It was all over by quarter past\n
 I was down in the sewer with some little lover\n
 When I peeked out from a manhole cover\n
 Wondering who turned the lights on\n

 Well, I got up and walked around\n
 And up and down the lonesome town\n
 I stood a-wondering which way to go\n
 I lit a cigarette on a parking meter and walked on down the road\n
 It was a normal day\n

 Well, I rung the fallout shelter bell\n
 And I leaned my head and I gave a yell\n
 “Give me a string bean, I’m a hungry man”\n
 A shotgun fired and away I ran\n
 I don’t blame them too much though, I know I look funny\n

 Down at the corner by a hot-dog stand\n
 I seen a man\n
 I said, “Howdy friend, I guess there’s just us two”\n
 He screamed a bit and away he flew\n
 Thought I was a Communist\n

 Well, I spied a girl and before she could leave\n
 “Let’s go and play Adam and Eve”\n
 I took her by the hand and my heart it was thumpin’\n
 When she said, “Hey man, you crazy or sumpin’\n
 You see what happened last time they started”\n

 Well, I seen a Cadillac window uptown\n
 And there was nobody aroun’\n
 I got into the driver’s seat\n
 And I drove down 42nd Street\n
 In my Cadillac. Good car to drive after a war\n

 Well, I remember seein’ some ad\n
 So I turned on my Conelrad\n
 But I didn’t pay my Con Ed bill\n
 So the radio didn’t work so well\n
 Turned on my record player—\n
 It was Rock-a-day Johnny singin’, “Tell Your Ma, Tell Your Pa\n
 Our Love’s A-gonna Grow Ooh-wah, Ooh-wah”\n

 I was feelin’ kinda lonesome and blue\n
 I needed somebody to talk to\n
 So I called up the operator of time\n
 Just to hear a voice of some kind\n
 “When you hear the beep it will be three o’clock”\n
 She said that for over an hour\n
 And I hung up\n

 Well, the doctor interrupted me just about then\n
 Sayin’, “Hey I’ve been havin’ the same old dreams\n
 But mine was a little different you see\n
 I dreamt that the only person left after the war was me\n
 I didn’t see you around”\n

 Well, now time passed and now it seems\n
 Everybody’s having them dreams\n
 Everybody sees themselves\n
 Walkin’ around with no one else\n
 Half of the people can be part right all of the time\n
 Some of the people can be all right part of the time\n
 But all of the people can’t be all right all of the time\n
 I think Abraham Lincoln said that\n
 “I’ll let you be in my dreams if I can be in yours”\n
 I said that\n

    </string>
    <string name="corrinacorrinalyrics">
        Corrina, Corrina\n
 Gal, where you been so long?\n
 Corrina, Corrina\n
 Gal, where you been so long?\n
 I been worr’in’ ’bout you, baby\n
 Baby, please come home\n

 I got a bird that whistles\n
 I got a bird that sings\n
 I got a bird that whistles\n
 I got a bird that sings\n
 But I ain’ a-got Corrina\n
 Life don’t mean a thing\n

 Corrina, Corrina\n
 Gal, you’re on my mind\n
 Corrina, Corrina\n
 Gal, you’re on my mind\n
 I’m a-thinkin’ ’bout you, baby\n
 I just can’t keep from crying.\n


    </string>
    <string name="honeyjustallowmeonemorechancelyrics">

        Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 To get along with you\n
 Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 Ah’ll do anything with you\n
 Well, I’m a-walkin’ down the road\n
 With my head in my hand\n
 I’m lookin’ for a woman\n
 Needs a worried man\n
 Just-a one kind favor I ask you\n
 ’Low me just-a one more chance\n

 Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 To ride your aeroplane\n
 Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 To ride your passenger train\n
 Well, I’ve been lookin’ all over\n
 For a gal like you\n
 I can’t find nobody\n
 So you’ll have to do\n
 Just-a one kind favor I ask you\n
 ’Low me just-a one more chance\n

 Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 To get along with you\n
 Honey, just allow me one more chance\n
 Ah’ll do anything with you\n
 Well, lookin’ for a woman\n
 That ain’t got no man\n
 Is just lookin’ for a needle\n
 That is lost in the sand\n
 Just-a one kind favor I ask you\n
 ’Low me just-a one more chance\n

    </string>
    <string name="ishallbefreewheelinglyrics">
Well, I took me a woman late last night
 I’s three-fourths drunk, she looked uptight
 She took off her wheel, took off her bell
 Took off her wig, said, “How do I smell?"
 I hot-footed it . .  bare-naked . .
 Out the window!
 Well, sometimes I might get drunk
 Walk like a duck and stomp like a skunk
 Don’t hurt me none, don’t hurt my pride
 ’Cause I got my little lady right by my side
 (Right there Proud as can be)
     I’s out there paintin’ on the old woodshed
 When a can a black paint it fell on my head
 I went down to scrub and rub
 But I had to sit in back of the tub
 (Cost a quarter
 And I had to get out quick . . .
 Someone wanted to come in and take a sauna)
     Well, my telephone rang it would not stop
 It’s President Kennedy callin’ me up
 He said, “My friend, Bob, what do we need to make the country grow?”
 I said, “My friend, John, Brigitte Bardot
 Anita Ekberg
 Sophia Loren”
 (Put ’em all in the same room with Ernest Borgnine!)
     Well, I got a woman sleeps on a cot
 She yells and hollers and squeals a lot
 Licks my face and tickles my ear
 Bends me over and buys me beer
 (She’s a honeymooner
 A June crooner
 A spoon feeder
 And a natural leader)
 Oh, there ain’t no use in me workin’ so heavy
 I got a woman who works on the levee
 Pumping that water up to her neck
 Every week she sends me a monthly check
 (She’s a humdinger
 Folk singer
 Dead ringer
 For a thing-a-muh jigger)
 Late one day in the middle of the week
 Eyes were closed I was half asleep
 I chased me a woman up the hill
 Right in the middle of an air-raid drill
 It was Little Bo Peep!
 (I jumped a fallout shelter
 I jumped a bean stalk
 I jumped a Ferris wheel)
 Now, the man on the stand he wants my vote
 He’s a-runnin’ for office on the ballot note
 He’s out there preachin’ in front of the steeple
 Tellin’ me he loves all kinds-a people
 (He’s eatin’ bagels
 He’s eatin’ pizza
 He’s eatin’ chitlins
 He’s eatin’ bullshit!)
 Oh, set me down on a television floor
 I’ll flip the channel to number four
 Out of the shower comes a grown-up man
 With a bottle of hair oil in his hand
     (It’s that greasy kid stuff
 What I want to know, Mr. Football Man, is
 What do you do about Willy Mays and Yul Brynner
 Charles de Gaulle
 And Robert Louis Stevenson?)
 Well, the funniest woman I ever seen
 Was the great-granddaughter of Mr. Clean
 She takes about fifteen baths a day
 Wants me to grow a cigar on my face
 (She’s a little bit heavy!)
 Well, ask me why I’m drunk alla time
 It levels my head and eases my mind
 I just walk along and stroll and sing
 I see better days and I do better things
 (I catch dinosaurs
 I make love to Elizabeth Taylor . . .
 Catch hell from Richard Burton!)


    </string>


</resources>