<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="likearollingstonelyrics">
        Once upon a time you dressed so fine\n
 You threw the bums a dime in your prime, didn’t you?\n
 People’d call, say, “Beware doll, you’re bound to fall”\n
 You thought they were all kiddin’ you\n
 You used to laugh about\n
 Everybody that was hangin’ out\n
 Now you don’t talk so loud\n
 Now you don’t seem so proud\n
 About having to be scrounging for your next meal\n

 How does it feel\n
 How does it feel\n
 To be without a home\n
 Like a complete unknown\n
 Like a rolling stone?\n

 You’ve gone to the finest school all right, Miss Lonely\n
 But you know you only used to get juiced in it\n
 And nobody has ever taught you how to live on the street\n
 And now you find out you’re gonna have to get used to it\n
 You said you’d never compromise\n
 With the mystery tramp, but now you realize\n
 He’s not selling any alibis\n
 As you stare into the vacuum of his eyes\n
 And ask him do you want to make a deal?\n

 How does it feel\n
 How does it feel\n
 To be on your own\n
 With no direction home\n
 Like a complete unknown\n
 Like a rolling stone?\n

 You never turned around to see the frowns on the jugglers and the clowns\n
 When they all come down and did tricks for you\n
 You never understood that it ain’t no good\n
 You shouldn’t let other people get your kicks for you\n
 You used to ride on the chrome horse with your diplomat\n
 Who carried on his shoulder a Siamese cat\n
 Ain’t it hard when you discover that\n
 He really wasn’t where it’s at\n
 After he took from you everything he could steal\n

 How does it feel\n
 How does it feel\n
 To be on your own\n
 With no direction home\n
 Like a complete unknown\n
 Like a rolling stone?\n

 Princess on the steeple and all the pretty people\n
 They’re drinkin’, thinkin’ that they got it made\n
 Exchanging all kinds of precious gifts and things\n
 But you’d better lift your diamond ring, you’d better pawn it babe\n
 You used to be so amused\n
 At Napoleon in rags and the language that he used\n
 Go to him now, he calls you, you can’t refuse\n
 When you got nothing, you got nothing to lose\n
 You’re invisible now, you got no secrets to conceal\n

 How does it feel\n
 How does it feel\n
 To be on your own\n
 With no direction home\n
 Like a complete unknown\n
 Like a rolling stone?\n


    </string>
<string name="ittakesalottolaughtittakesatraintocrylyrics">
 Well, I ride on a mailtrain, baby\n
 Can’t buy a thrill\n
 Well, I’ve been up all night, baby\n
 Leanin’ on the windowsill\n
 Well, if I die\n
 On top of the hill\n
 And if I don’t make it\n
 You know my baby will\n

 Don’t the moon look good, mama\n
 Shinin’ through the trees?\n
 Don’t the brakeman look good, mama\n
 Flagging down the “Double E?”\n
 Don’t the sun look good\n
 Goin’ down over the sea?\n
 Don’t my gal look fine\n
 When she’s comin’ after me?\n

 Now the wintertime is coming\n
 The windows are filled with frost\n
 I went to tell everybody\n
 But I could not get across\n
 Well, I wanna be your lover, baby\n
 I don’t wanna be your boss\n
 Don’t say I never warned you\n
 When your train gets lost\n


</string>
    <string name="tombstoneblueslyrics">
The sweet pretty things are in bed now of course\n
 The city fathers they’re trying to endorse\n
 The reincarnation of Paul Revere’s horse\n
 But the town has no need to be nervous\n

 The ghost of Belle Starr she hands down her wits\n
 To Jezebel the nun she violently knits\n
 A bald wig for Jack the Ripper who sits\n
 At the head of the chamber of commerce\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

 The hysterical bride in the penny arcade\n
 Screaming she moans, “I’ve just been made”\n
 Then sends out for the doctor who pulls down the shade\n
 Says, “My advice is to not let the boys in”\n

 Now the medicine man comes and he shuffles inside\n
 He walks with a swagger and he says to the bride\n
 “Stop all this weeping, swallow your pride\n
 You will not die, it’s not poison”\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

 Well, John the Baptist after torturing a thief\n
 Looks up at his hero the Commander-in-Chief\n
 Saying, “Tell me great hero, but please make it brief\n
 Is there a hole for me to get sick in?”\n

 The Commander-in-Chief answers him while chasing a fly\n
 Saying, “Death to all those who would whimper and cry”\n
 And dropping a barbell he points to the sky\n
 Saying, “The sun’s not yellow it’s chicken”\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

 The king of the Philistines his soldiers to save\n
 Puts jawbones on their tombstones and flatters their graves\n
 Puts the pied pipers in prison and fattens the slaves\n
 Then sends them out to the jungle\n

 Gypsy Davey with a blowtorch he burns out their camps\n
 With his faithful slave Pedro behind him he tramps\n
 With a fantastic collection of stamps\n
 To win friends and influence his uncle\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

 The geometry of innocence flesh on the bone\n
 Causes Galileo’s math book to get thrown\n
 At Delilah who sits worthlessly alone\n
 But the tears on her cheeks are from laughter\n

 Now I wish I could give Brother Bill his great thrill\n
 I would set him in chains at the top of the hill\n
 Then send out for some pillars and Cecil B. DeMille\n
 He could die happily ever after\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

 Where Ma Rainey and Beethoven once unwrapped their bedroll\n
 Tuba players now rehearse around the flagpole\n
 And the National Bank at a profit sells road maps for the soul\n
 To the old folks home and the college\n

 Now I wish I could write you a melody so plain\n
 That could hold you dear lady from going insane\n
 That could ease you and cool you and cease the pain\n
 Of your useless and pointless knowledge\n

 Mama’s in the fact’ry\n
 She ain’t got no shoes\n
 Daddy’s in the alley\n
 He’s lookin’ for the fuse\n
 I’m in the streets\n
 With the tombstone blues\n

    </string>

    <string name="balladofathinmanlyrics">
You walk into the room\n
 With your pencil in your hand\n
 You see somebody naked\n
 And you say, “Who is that man?”\n
 You try so hard\n
 But you don’t understand\n
 Just what you’ll say\n
 When you get home\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 You raise up your head\n
 And you ask, “Is this where it is?”\n
 And somebody points to you and says\n
 “It’s his”\n
 And you say, “What’s mine?”\n
 And somebody else says, “Where what is?”\n
 And you say, “Oh my God\n
 Am I here all alone?”\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 You hand in your ticket\n
 And you go watch the geek\n
 Who immediately walks up to you\n
 When he hears you speak\n
 And says, “How does it feel\n
 To be such a freak?”\n
 And you say, “Impossible”\n
 As he hands you a bone\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 You have many contacts\n
 Among the lumberjacks\n
 To get you facts\n
 When someone attacks your imagination\n
 But nobody has any respect\n
 Anyway they already expect you\n
 To just give a check\n
 To tax-deductible charity organizations\n

 You’ve been with the professors\n
 And they’ve all liked your looks\n
 With great lawyers you have\n
 Discussed lepers and crooks\n
 You’ve been through all of\n
 F. Scott Fitzgerald’s books\n
 You’re very well read\n
 It’s well known\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 Well, the sword swallower, he comes up to you\n
 And then he kneels\n
 He crosses himself\n
 And then he clicks his high heels\n
 And without further notice\n
 He asks you how it feels\n
 And he says, “Here is your throat back\n
 Thanks for the loan”\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 Now you see this one-eyed midget\n
 Shouting the word “NOW”\n
 And you say, “For what reason?”\n
 And he says, “How?”\n
 And you say, “What does this mean?”\n
 And he screams back, “You’re a cow\n
 Give me some milk\n
 Or else go home”\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n

 Well, you walk into the room\n
 Like a camel and then you frown\n
 You put your eyes in your pocket\n
 And your nose on the ground\n
 There ought to be a law\n
 Against you comin’ around\n
 You should be made\n
 To wear earphones\n

 Because something is happening here\n
 But you don’t know what it is\n
 Do you, Mister Jones?\n


    </string>
 <string name="frombuick6lyrics">
  I got this graveyard woman, you know she keeps my kid\n
 But my soulful mama, you know she keeps me hid\n
 She’s a junkyard angel and she always gives me bread\n
 Well, if I go down dyin’, you know she bound to put a blanket on my bed.\n

 Well, when the pipeline gets broken and I’m lost on the river bridge\n
 I’m cracked up on the highway and on the water’s edge\n
 She comes down the thruway ready to sew me up with thread\n
 Well, if I go down dyin’, you know she bound to put a blanket on my bed.\n

 Well, she don’t make me nervous, she don’t talk too much\n
 She walks like Bo Diddley and she don’t need no crutch\n
 She keeps this four-ten all loaded with lead\n
 Well, if I go down dyin’, you know she bound to put a blanket on my bed.\n
 
 Well, you know I need a steam shovel mama to keep away the dead\n
 I need a dump truck mama to unload my head\n
 She brings me everything and more, and just like I said\n
 Well, if I go down dyin’, you know she bound to put a blanket on my bed.\n

 </string>
    <string name="queenjaneapproximatelylyrics">
When your mother sends back all your invitations\n
 And your father to your sister he explains\n
 That you’re tired of yourself and all of your creations\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n

 Now when all of the flower ladies want back what they have lent you\n
 And the smell of their roses does not remain\n
 And all of your children start to resent you\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n

 Now when all the clowns that you have commissioned\n
 Have died in battle or in vain\n
 And you’re sick of all this repetition\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n

 When all of your advisers heave their plastic\n
 At your feet to convince you of your pain\n
 Trying to prove that your conclusions should be more drastic\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n

 Now when all the bandits that you turned your other cheek to\n
 All lay down their bandanas and complain\n
 And you want somebody you don’t have to speak to\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n
 Won’t you come see me, Queen Jane?\n

    </string>
    <string name="highway61revisitedlyrics">
Oh God said to Abraham, “Kill me a son”\n
 Abe says, “Man, you must be puttin’ me on”\n
 God say, “No.” Abe say, “What?”\n
 God say, “You can do what you want Abe, but\n
 The next time you see me comin’ you better run”\n
 Well Abe says, “Where do you want this killin’ done?”\n
 God says, “Out on Highway 61”\n
     Well Georgia Sam he had a bloody nose\n
 Welfare Department they wouldn’t give him no clothes\n
 He asked poor Howard where can I go\n
 Howard said there’s only one place I know\n
 Sam said tell me quick man I got to run\n
 Ol’ Howard just pointed with his gun\n
 And said that way down on Highway 61\n
 Well Mack the Finger said to Louie the King\n
 I got forty red white and blue shoestrings\n
 And a thousand telephones that don’t ring\n
 Do you know where I can get rid of these things\n
 And Louie the King said let me think for a minute son\n
 And he said yes I think it can be easily done\n
 Just take everything down to Highway 61\n
 Now the fifth daughter on the twelfth night\n
 Told the first father that things weren’t right\n
 My complexion she said is much too white\n
 He said come here and step into the light he says hmm you’re right\n
 Let me tell the second mother this has been done\n
 But the second mother was with the seventh son\n
 And they were both out on Highway 61\n
 Now the rovin’ gambler he was very bored\n
 He was tryin’ to create a next world war\n
 He found a promoter who nearly fell off the floor\n
 He said I never engaged in this kind of thing before\n
 But yes I think it can be very easily done\n
 We’ll just put some bleachers out in the sun\n
 And have it on Highway 61\n


    </string>
    <string name="desolationrowlyrics">
They’re selling postcards of the hanging\n
 They’re painting the passports brown\n
 The beauty parlor is filled with sailors\n
 The circus is in town\n
 Here comes the blind commissioner\n
 They’ve got him in a trance\n
 One hand is tied to the tight-rope walker\n
 The other is in his pants\n
 And the riot squad they’re restless\n
 They need somewhere to go\n
 As Lady and I look out tonight\n
 From Desolation Row\n

 Cinderella, she seems so easy\n
 “It takes one to know one,” she smiles\n
 And puts her hands in her back pockets\n
 Bette Davis style\n
 And in comes Romeo, he’s moaning\n
 “You Belong to Me I Believe”\n
 And someone says, “You’re in the wrong place my friend\n
 You better leave”\n
 And the only sound that’s left\n
 After the ambulances go\n
 Is Cinderella sweeping up\n
 On Desolation Row\n

 Now the moon is almost hidden\n
 The stars are beginning to hide\n
 The fortune-telling lady\n
 Has even taken all her things inside\n
 All except for Cain and Abel\n
 And the hunchback of Notre Dame\n
 Everybody is making love\n
 Or else expecting rain\n
 And the Good Samaritan, he’s dressing\n
 He’s getting ready for the show\n
 He’s going to the carnival tonight\n
 On Desolation Row\n

 Now Ophelia, she’s ’neath the window\n
 For her I feel so afraid\n
 On her twenty-second birthday\n
 She already is an old maid\n
 To her, death is quite romantic\n
 She wears an iron vest\n
 Her profession’s her religion\n
 Her sin is her lifelessness\n
 And though her eyes are fixed upon\n
 Noah’s great rainbow\n
 She spends her time peeking\n
 Into Desolation Row\n

 Einstein, disguised as Robin Hood\n
 With his memories in a trunk\n
 Passed this way an hour ago\n
 With his friend, a jealous monk\n
 He looked so immaculately frightful\n
 As he bummed a cigarette\n
 Then he went off sniffing drainpipes\n
 And reciting the alphabet\n
 Now you would not think to look at him\n
 But he was famous long ago\n
 For playing the electric violin\n
 On Desolation Row\n

 Dr. Filth, he keeps his world\n
 Inside of a leather cup\n
 But all his sexless patients\n
 They’re trying to blow it up\n
 Now his nurse, some local loser\n
 She’s in charge of the cyanide hole\n
 And she also keeps the cards that read\n
 “Have Mercy on His Soul”\n
 They all play on pennywhistles\n
 You can hear them blow\n
 If you lean your head out far enough\n
 From Desolation Row\n

 Across the street they’ve nailed the curtains\n
 They’re getting ready for the feast\n
 The Phantom of the Opera\n
 A perfect image of a priest\n
 They’re spoonfeeding Casanova\n
 To get him to feel more assured\n
 Then they’ll kill him with self-confidence\n
 After poisoning him with words\n
 And the Phantom’s shouting to skinny girls\n
 “Get Outa Here If You Don’t Know\n
 Casanova is just being punished for going\n
 To Desolation Row”\n

 Now at midnight all the agents\n
 And the superhuman crew\n
 Come out and round up everyone\n
 That knows more than they do\n
 Then they bring them to the factory\n
 Where the heart-attack machine\n
 Is strapped across their shoulders\n
 And then the kerosene\n
 Is brought down from the castles\n
 By insurance men who go\n
 Check to see that nobody is escaping\n
 To Desolation Row\n

 Praise be to Nero’s Neptune\n
 The Titanic sails at dawn\n
 And everybody’s shouting\n
 “Which Side Are You On?”\n
 And Ezra Pound and T. S. Eliot\n
 Fighting in the captain’s tower\n
 While calypso singers laugh at them\n
 And fishermen hold flowers\n
 Between the windows of the sea\n
 Where lovely mermaids flow\n
 And nobody has to think too much\n
 About Desolation Row\n

 Yes, I received your letter yesterday\n
 (About the time the doorknob broke)\n
 When you asked how I was doing\n
 Was that some kind of joke?\n
 All these people that you mention\n
 Yes, I know them, they’re quite lame\n
 I had to rearrange their faces\n
 And give them all another name\n
 Right now I can’t read too good\n
 Don’t send me no more letters no\n
 Not unless you mail them\n
 From Desolation Row\n



    </string>
















</resources>