<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="jokermanlyrics">
        Standing on the waters casting your bread\n
 While the eyes of the idol with the iron head are glowing\n
 Distant ships sailing into the mist\n
 You were born with a snake in both of your fists while a hurricane was blowing\n
 Freedom just around the corner for you\n
 But with the truth so far off, what good will it do?\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

 So swiftly the sun sets in the sky\n
 You rise up and say goodbye to no one\n
 Fools rush in where angels fear to tread\n
 Both of their futures, so full of dread, you don’t show one\n
 Shedding off one more layer of skin\n
 Keeping one step ahead of the persecutor within\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

 You’re a man of the mountains, you can walk on the clouds\n
 Manipulator of crowds, you’re a dream twister\n
 You’re going to Sodom and Gomorrah\n
 But what do you care? Ain’t nobody there would want to marry your sister\n
 Friend to the martyr, a friend to the woman of shame\n
 You look into the fiery furnace, see the rich man without any name\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

 Well, the Book of Leviticus and Deuteronomy\n
 The law of the jungle and the sea are your only teachers\n
 In the smoke of the twilight on a milk-white steed\n
 Michelangelo indeed could’ve carved out your features\n
 Resting in the fields, far from the turbulent space\n
 Half asleep near the stars with a small dog licking your face\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

 Well, the rifleman’s stalking the sick and the lame\n
 Preacherman seeks the same, who’ll get there first is uncertain\n
 Nightsticks and water cannons, tear gas, padlocks\n
 Molotov cocktails and rocks behind every curtain\n
 False-hearted judges dying in the webs that they spin\n
 Only a matter of time ’til night comes steppin’ in\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

 It’s a shadowy world, skies are slippery grey\n
 A woman just gave birth to a prince today and dressed him in scarlet\n
 He’ll put the priest in his pocket, put the blade to the heat\n
 Take the motherless children off the street and place them at the feet of a harlot\n
 Oh, Jokerman, you know what he wants\n
 Oh, Jokerman, you don’t show any response\n

 Jokerman dance to the nightingale tune\n
 Bird fly high by the light of the moon\n
 Oh, oh, oh, Jokerman\n

    </string>

    <string name="sweetheartlikeyoulyrics">
Well, the pressure’s down, the boss ain’t here\n
 He gone North, he ain’t around\n
 They say that vanity got the best of him\n
 But he sure left here after sundown\n
 By the way, that’s a cute hat\n
 And that smile’s so hard to resist\n
 But what’s a sweetheart like you doin’ in a dump like this?\n

 You know, I once knew a woman who looked like you\n
 She wanted a whole man, not just a half\n
 She used to call me sweet daddy when I was only a child\n
 You kind of remind me of her when you laugh\n
 In order to deal in this game, got to make the queen disappear\n
 It’s done with a flick of the wrist\n
 What’s a sweetheart like you doin’ in a dump like this?\n

 You know, a woman like you should be at home\n
 That’s where you belong\n
 Watching out for someone who loves you true\n
 Who would never do you wrong\n
 Just how much abuse will you be able to take?\n
 Well, there’s no way to tell by that first kiss\n
 What’s a sweetheart like you doin’ in a dump like this?\n

 You know you can make a name for yourself\n
 You can hear them tires squeal\n
 You can be known as the most beautiful woman\n
 Who ever crawled across cut glass to make a deal\n

 You know, news of you has come down the line\n
 Even before ya came in the door\n
 They say in your father’s house, there’s many mansions\n
 Each one of them got a fireproof floor\n
 Snap out of it, baby, people are jealous of you\n
 They smile to your face, but behind your back they hiss\n
 What’s a sweetheart like you doin’ in a dump like this?\n

 Got to be an important person to be in here, honey\n
 Got to have done some evil deed\n
 Got to have your own harem when you come in the door\n
 Got to play your harp until your lips bleed\n

 They say that patriotism is the last refuge\n
 To which a scoundrel clings\n
 Steal a little and they throw you in jail\n
 Steal a lot and they make you king\n
 There’s only one step down from here, baby\n
 It’s called the land of permanent bliss\n
 What’s a sweetheart like you doin’ in a dump like this?\n


    </string>
<string name="neighborhoodbullylyrics">

Well, the neighborhood bully, he’s just one man\n
 His enemies say he’s on their land\n
 They got him outnumbered about a million to one\n
 He got no place to escape to, no place to run\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 The neighborhood bully just lives to survive\n
 He’s criticized and condemned for being alive\n
 He’s not supposed to fight back, he’s supposed to have thick skin\n
 He’s supposed to lay down and die when his door is kicked in\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 The neighborhood bully been driven out of every land\n
 He’s wandered the earth an exiled man\n
 Seen his family scattered, his people hounded and torn\n
 He’s always on trial for just being born\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 Well, he knocked out a lynch mob, he was criticized\n
 Old women condemned him, said he should apologize.\n
 Then he destroyed a bomb factory, nobody was glad\n
 The bombs were meant for him. He was supposed to feel bad\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 Well, the chances are against it and the odds are slim\n
 That he’ll live by the rules that the world makes for him\n
 ’Cause there’s a noose at his neck and a gun at his back\n
 And a license to kill him is given out to every maniac\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 He got no allies to really speak of\n
 What he gets he must pay for, he don’t get it out of love\n
 He buys obsolete weapons and he won’t be denied\n
 But no one sends flesh and blood to fight by his side\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 Well, he’s surrounded by pacifists who all want peace\n
 They pray for it nightly that the bloodshed must cease\n
 Now, they wouldn’t hurt a fly. To hurt one they would weep\n
 They lay and they wait for this bully to fall asleep\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 Every empire that’s enslaved him is gone\n
 Egypt and Rome, even the great Babylon\n
 He’s made a garden of paradise in the desert sand\n
 In bed with nobody, under no one’s command\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 Now his holiest books have been trampled upon\n
 No contract he signed was worth what it was written on\n
 He took the crumbs of the world and he turned it into wealth\n
 Took sickness and disease and he turned it into health\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 What’s anybody indebted to him for?\n
 Nothin’, they say. He just likes to cause war\n
 Pride and prejudice and superstition indeed\n
 They wait for this bully like a dog waits to feed\n
 He’s the neighborhood bully\n

 What has he done to wear so many scars?\n
 Does he change the course of rivers? Does he pollute the moon and stars?\n
 Neighborhood bully, standing on the hill\n
 Running out the clock, time standing still\n
 Neighborhood bully\n

</string>

    <string name="lisencetokilllyrics">
Man thinks ’cause he rules the earth he can do with it as he please\n
 And if things don’t change soon, he will\n
 Oh, man has invented his doom\n
 First step was touching the moon\n

 Now, there’s a woman on my block\n
 She just sit there as the night grows still\n
 She say who gonna take away his license to kill?\n

 Now, they take him and they teach him and they groom him for life\n
 And they set him on a path where he’s bound to get ill\n
 Then they bury him with stars\n
 Sell his body like they do used cars\n

 Now, there’s a woman on my block\n
 She just sit there facin’ the hill\n
 She say who gonna take away his license to kill?\n

 Now, he’s hell-bent for destruction, he’s afraid and confused\n
 And his brain has been mismanaged with great skill\n
 All he believes are his eyes\n
 And his eyes, they just tell him lies\n

 But there’s a woman on my block\n
 Sitting there in a cold chill\n
 She say who gonna take away his license to kill?\n

 Ya may be a noisemaker, spirit maker\n
 Heartbreaker, backbreaker\n
 Leave no stone unturned\n
 May be an actor in a plot\n
 That might be all that you got\n
 ’Til your error you clearly learn\n

 Now he worships at an altar of a stagnant pool\n
 And when he sees his reflection, he’s fulfilled\n
 Oh, man is opposed to fair play\n
 He wants it all and he wants it his way\n

 Now, there’s a woman on my block\n
 She just sit there as the night grows still\n
 She say who gonna take away his license to kill?\n


    </string>
    <string name="manofpeacelyrics">
Look out your window, baby, there’s a scene you’d like to catch\n
 The band is playing “Dixie,” a man got his hand outstretched\n
 Could be the Führer\n
 Could be the local priest\n
 You know sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 He got a sweet gift of gab, he got a harmonious tongue\n
 He knows every song of love that ever has been sung\n
 Good intentions can be evil\n
 Both hands can be full of grease\n
 You know that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 Well, first he’s in the background, then he’s in the front\n
 Both eyes are looking like they’re on a rabbit hunt\n
 Nobody can see through him\n
 No, not even the Chief of Police\n
 You know that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 Well, he catch you when you’re hoping for a glimpse of the sun\n
 Catch you when your troubles feel like they weigh a ton\n
 He could be standing next to you\n
 The person that you’d notice least\n
 I hear that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 Well, he can be fascinating, he can be dull\n
 He can ride down Niagara Falls in the barrels of your skull\n
 I can smell something cooking\n
 I can tell there’s going to be a feast\n
 You know that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 He’s a great humanitarian, he’s a great philanthropist\n
 He knows just where to touch you, honey, and how you like to be kissed\n
 He’ll put both his arms around you\n
 You can feel the tender touch of the beast\n
 You know that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 Well, the howling wolf will howl tonight, the king snake will crawl\n
 Trees that’ve stood for a thousand years suddenly will fall\n
 Wanna get married? Do it now\n
 Tomorrow all activity will cease\n
 You know that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n

 Somewhere Mama’s weeping for her blue-eyed boy\n
 She’s holding them little white shoes and that little broken toy\n
 And he’s following a star\n
 The same one them three men followed from the East\n
 I hear that sometimes Satan comes as a man of peace\n



    </string>
    <string name="unionsundownlyrics">
Well, my shoes, they come from Singapore\n
 My flashlight’s from Taiwan\n
 My tablecloth’s from Malaysia\n
 My belt buckle’s from the Amazon\n
 You know, this shirt I wear comes from the Philippines\n
 And the car I drive is a Chevrolet\n
 It was put together down in Argentina\n
 By a guy makin’ thirty cents a day\n

 Well, it’s sundown on the union\n
 And what’s made in the U.S.A.\n
 Sure was a good idea\n
 ’Til greed got in the way\n

 Well, this silk dress is from Hong Kong\n
 And the pearls are from Japan\n
 Well, the dog collar’s from India\n
 And the flower pot’s from Pakistan\n
 All the furniture, it says “Made in Brazil”\n
 Where a woman, she slaved for sure\n
 Bringin’ home thirty cents a day to a family of twelve\n
 You know, that’s a lot of money to her\n

 Well, it’s sundown on the union\n
 And what’s made in the U.S.A.\n
 Sure was a good idea\n
 ’Til greed got in the way\n

 Well, you know, lots of people complainin’ that there is no work\n
 I say, “Why you say that for\n
 When nothin’ you got is U.S.–made?”\n
 They don’t make nothin’ here no more\n
 You know, capitalism is above the law\n
 It say, “It don’t count ’less it sells”\n
 When it costs too much to build it at home\n
 You just build it cheaper someplace else\n

 Well, it’s sundown on the union\n
 And what’s made in the U.S.A.\n
 Sure was a good idea\n
 ’Til greed got in the way\n

 Well, the job that you used to have\n
 They gave it to somebody down in El Salvador\n
 The unions are big business, friend\n
 And they’re goin’ out like a dinosaur\n
 They used to grow food in Kansas\n
 Now they want to grow it on the moon and eat it raw\n
 I can see the day coming when even your home garden\n
 Is gonna be against the law\n

 Well, it’s sundown on the union\n
 And what’s made in the U.S.A.\n
 Sure was a good idea\n
 ’Til greed got in the way\n

 Democracy don’t rule the world\n
 You’d better get that in your head\n
 This world is ruled by violence\n
 But I guess that’s better left unsaid\n
 From Broadway to the Milky Way\n
 That’s a lot of territory indeed\n
 And a man’s gonna do what he has to do\n
 When he’s got a hungry mouth to feed\n

 Well, it’s sundown on the union\n
 And what’s made in the U.S.A.\n
 Sure was a good idea\n
 ’Til greed got in the way\n


    </string>
    <string name="iandilyrics">
Been so long since a strange woman\n
     has slept in my bed\n
 Look how sweet she sleeps, \n
     how free must be her dreams\n
 In another lifetime \n
     she must have owned the world,\n
     or been faithfully wed\n
 To some righteous king who wrote psalms beside moonlit streams\n

 I and I\n
 In creation where one’s nature\n
     neither honors nor forgives\n
 I and I\n
 One says to the other, \n
     no man sees my face and lives\n
 Think I’ll go out and go for a walk\n
 Not much happenin’ here, nothin’ ever does\n
 Besides, if she wakes up now,\n
     she’ll just want me to talk\n
 I got nothin’ to say, \n
     ’specially about whatever was\n

 I and I\n
 In creation where one’s nature neither honors nor forgives\n
 I and I\n
 One says to the other,\n
     no man sees my face and lives\n

 Took an untrodden path once, \n
     where the swift don’t win the race\n
 It goes to the worthy, \n
     who can divide the word of truth\n
 Took a stranger to teach me,\n
     to look into justice’s beautiful face\n
 And to see an eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth\n

 I and I\n
 In creation where one’s nature neither honors nor forgives\n
 I and I\n
 One says to the other, \n
     no man sees my face and lives\n

 Outside of two men on a train platform there’s nobody in sight\n
 They’re waiting for spring to come,\n
     smoking down the track\n
 The world could come to an end tonight, \n
     but that’s all right\n
 She should still be there sleepin’ when I get back\n

 I and I\n
 In creation where one’s nature neither honors nor forgives\n
 I and I\n
 One says to the other,\n
     no man sees my face and lives\n

 Noontime, and I’m still pushin’ myself along the road,\n
     the darkest part\n
 Into the narrow lanes,\n
     I can’t stumble or stay put\n
 Someone else is speakin’ with my mouth, \n
     but I’m listening only to my heart\n
 I’ve made shoes for everyone,\n
     even you, while I still go barefoot\n

 I and I\n
 In creation where one’s nature neither honors nor forgives\n
 I and I\n
 One says to the other,\n
     no man sees my face and lives\n



    </string>
    <string name="dontfallapartonmelyrics">
Just a minute before you leave, girl\n
 Just a minute before you touch the door\n
 What is it that you’re trying to achieve, girl?\n
 Do you think we can talk about it some more?\n
 You know, the streets are filled with vipers\n
 Who’ve lost all ray of hope\n
 You know, it ain’t even safe no more\n
 In the palace of the Pope\n

 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 I just don’t think that I could handle it\n
 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 Yesterday’s just a memory\n
 Tomorrow is never what it’s supposed to be\n
 And I need you, yeah\n

 Come over here from over there, girl\n
 Sit down here. You can have my chair\n
 I can’t see us goin’ anywhere, girl\n
 The only place open is a thousand miles away and I can’t take you there\n
 I wish I’d have been a doctor\n
 Maybe I’d have saved some life that had been lost\n
 Maybe I’d have done some good in the world\n
 ’Stead of burning every bridge I crossed\n

 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 I just don’t think that I could handle it\n
 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 Yesterday’s just a memory\n
 Tomorrow is never what it’s supposed to be\n
 And I need you, oh, yeah\n

 I ain’t too good at conversation, girl\n
 So you might not know exactly how I feel\n
 But if I could, I’d bring you to the mountaintop, girl\n
 And build you a house made out of stainless steel\n
 But it’s like I’m stuck inside a painting\n
 That’s hanging in the Louvre\n
 My throat start to tickle and my nose itches\n
 But I know that I can’t move\n

 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 I just don’t think that I could handle it\n
 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 Yesterday’s gone but the past lives on\n
 Tomorrow’s just one step beyond\n
 And I need you, oh, yeah\n

 Who are these people who are walking towards you?\n
 Do you know them or will there be a fight?\n
 With their humorless smiles so easy to see through\n
 Can they tell you what’s wrong from what’s right?\n
 Do you remember St. James Street\n
 Where you blew Jackie P.’s mind?\n
 You were so fine, Clark Gable would have fell at your feet\n
 And laid his life on the line\n

 Let’s try to get beneath the surface waste, girl\n
 No more booby traps and bombs\n
 No more decadence and charm\n
 No more affection that’s misplaced, girl\n
 No more mudcake creatures lying in your arms\n
 What about that millionaire with the drumsticks in his pants?\n
 He looked so baffled and so bewildered\n
 When he played and we didn’t dance\n

 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 I just don’t think that I could handle it\n
 Don’t fall apart on me tonight\n
 Yesterday’s just a memory\n
 Tomorrow is never what it’s supposed to be\n
 And I need you, yeah\n



    </string>













</resources>