<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="asatisfiedmindlyrics">
        How many times have you heard someone say\n
 If I had his money I\'d do things my way\n
 Hmm, but little they know\n
 Hmm, it\'s so hard to find\n
 One rich man in ten with a satisfied mind.\n

 Hmm, once I was wadding in fortune and fame\n
 Everything that I dreamed of to get a start in lifes game\n
 But suddenly it happened\n
 Hmm, I lost every dime\n
 But I\'m richer by far with a satisfied mind.\n

 Hmm, when my life is over and my time has run out\n
 My friends and my love ones\n
 I\'ll leave there ain\'t no doubt\n
 But one thing for certain\n
 When it comes my time\n
 I\'ll leave this old world with a satisfied mind.\n


    </string>
    <string name="savedlyrics">
I was blinded by the devil\n
 Born already ruined\n
 Stone-cold dead\n
 As I stepped out of the womb\n
 By His grace I have been touched\n
 By His word I have been healed\n
 By His hand I’ve been delivered\n
 By His spirit I’ve been sealed\n

 I’ve been saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 Saved\n
 And I’m so glad\n
 Yes, I’m so glad\n
 I’m so glad\n
 So glad\n
 I want to thank You, Lord\n
 I just want to thank You, Lord\n
 Thank You, Lord\n

 By His truth I can be upright\n
 By His strength I do endure\n
 By His power I’ve been lifted\n
 In His love I am secure\n
 He bought me with a price\n
 Freed me from the pit\n
 Full of emptiness and wrath\n
 And the fire that burns in it\n

 I’ve been saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 Saved\n
 And I’m so glad\n
 Yes, I’m so glad\n
 I’m so glad\n
 So glad\n
 I want to thank You, Lord\n
 I just want to thank You, Lord\n
 Thank You, Lord\n

 Nobody to rescue me\n
 Nobody would dare\n
 I was going down for the last time\n
 But by His mercy I’ve been spared\n
 Not by works\n
 But by faith in Him who called\n
 For so long I’ve been hindered\n
 For so long I’ve been stalled\n

 I’ve been saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 By the blood of the lamb\n
 Saved\n
 Saved\n
 And I’m so glad\n
 Yes, I’m so glad\n
 I’m so glad\n
 So glad\n
 I want to thank You, Lord\n
 I just want to thank You, Lord\n
 Thank You, Lord\n


    </string>
    <string name="covenantwomenlyrics">
Covenant woman got a contract with the Lord\n
 Way up yonder, great will be her reward\n
 Covenant woman, shining like a morning star\n
 I know I can trust you to stay where you are\n

 And I just got to tell you\n
 I do intend\n
 To stay closer than any friend\n
 I just got to thank you\n
 Once again\n
 For making your prayers known\n
 Unto heaven for me\n
 And to you, always, so grateful\n
 I will forever be\n

 I’ve been broken, shattered like an empty cup\n
 I’m just waiting on the Lord to rebuild and fill me up\n
 And I know He will do it ’cause He’s faithful and He’s true\n
 He must have loved me so much to send me someone as fine as you\n

 And I just got to tell you\n
 I do intend\n
 To stay closer than any friend\n
 I just got to thank you\n
 Once again\n
 For making your prayers known\n
 Unto heaven for me\n
 And to you, always, so grateful\n
 I will forever be\n

 Covenant woman, intimate little girl\n
 Who knows those most secret things of me that are hidden from the world\n
 You know we are strangers in a land we’re passing through\n
 I’ll always be right by your side, I’ve got a covenant too\n

 And I just got to tell you\n
 I do intend\n
 To stay closer than any friend\n
 I just got to thank you\n
 Once again\n
 For making your prayers known\n
 Unto heaven for me\n
 And to you, always, so grateful\n
 I will forever be\n

    </string>
    <string name="whatcanidoforyoulyrics">
You have given everything to me\n
 What can I do for You?\n
 You have given me eyes to see\n
 What can I do for You?\n

 Pulled me out of bondage and You made me renewed inside\n
 Filled up a hunger that had always been denied\n
 Opened up a door no man can shut and You opened it up so wide\n
 And You’ve chosen me to be among the few\n
 What can I do for You?\n

 You have laid down Your life for me\n
 What can I do for You?\n
 You have explained every mystery\n
 What can I do for You?\n

 Soon as a man is born, you know the sparks begin to fly\n
 He gets wise in his own eyes and he’s made to believe a lie\n
 Who would deliver him from the death he’s bound to die?\n
 Well, You’ve done it all and there’s no more anyone can pretend to do\n
 What can I do for You?\n

 You have given all there is to give\n
 What can I do for You?\n
 You have given me life to live\n
 How can I live for You?\n

 I know all about poison, I know all about fiery darts\n
 I don’t care how rough the road is, show me where it starts\n
 Whatever pleases You, tell it to my heart\n
 Well, I don’t deserve it but I sure did make it through\n
 What can I do for You?\n



    </string>
    <string name="solidrocklyrics">
Well, I’m hangin’ on to a solid rock\n
 Made before the foundation of the world\n
 And I won’t let go, and I can’t let go, won’t let go\n
 And I can’t let go, won’t let go and I can’t let go no more\n
 For me He was chastised, for me He was hated\n
 For me He was rejected by a world that He created\n
 Nations are angry, cursed are some\n
 People are expecting a false peace to come\n

 Well, I’m hangin’ on to a solid rock\n
 Made before the foundation of the world\n
 And I won’t let go and I can’t let go, won’t let go\n
 And I can’t let go, won’t let go and I can’t let go no more\n

 It’s the ways of the flesh to war against the spirit\n
 Twenty-four hours a day you can feel it and you can hear it\n
 Using all the devices under the sun\n
 And He never give up ’til the battle’s lost or won\n

 Well, I’m hangin’ on to a solid rock\n
 Made before the foundation of the world\n
 And I won’t let go and I can’t let go, won’t let go\n
 And I can’t let go, won’t let go and I can’t let go no more\n



    </string>
    <string name="pressingonlyrics">
Well I’m pressing on\n
 Yes, I’m pressing on\n
 Well I’m pressing on\n
 To the higher calling of my Lord\n

 Many try to stop me, shake me up in my mind\n
 Say, “Prove to me that He is Lord, show me a sign”\n
 What kind of sign they need when it all come from within\n
 When what’s lost has been found, what’s to come has already been?\n

 Well I’m pressing on\n
 Yes, I’m pressing on\n
 Well I’m pressing on\n
 To the higher calling of my Lord\n

 Shake the dust off of your feet, don’t look back\n
 Nothing now can hold you down, nothing that you lack\n
 Temptation’s not an easy thing, Adam given the devil reign\n
 Because he sinned I got no choice, it run in my vein\n

 Well I’m pressing on\n
 Yes, I’m pressing on\n
 Well I’m pressing on\n
 To the higher calling of my Lord\n



    </string>
    <string name="inthegardenlyrics">
When they came for Him in the garden, did they know?\n
 When they came for Him in the garden, did they know?\n
 Did they know He was the Son of God, did they know that He was Lord?\n
 Did they hear when He told Peter, “Peter, put up your sword”?\n
 When they came for Him in the garden, did they know?\n
 When they came for Him in the garden, did they know?\n

 When He spoke to them in the city, did they hear?\n
 When He spoke to them in the city, did they hear?\n
 Nicodemus came at night so he wouldn’t be seen by men\n
 Saying, “Master, tell me why a man must be born again”\n
 When He spoke to them in the city, did they hear?\n
 When He spoke to them in the city, did they hear?\n

 When He healed the blind and crippled, did they see?\n
 When He healed the blind and crippled, did they see?\n
 When He said, “Pick up your bed and walk, why must you criticize?\n
 Same thing My Father do, I can do likewise”\n
 When He healed the blind and crippled, did they see?\n
 When He healed the blind and crippled, did they see?\n

 Did they speak out against Him, did they dare?\n
 Did they speak out against Him, did they dare?\n
 The multitude wanted to make Him king, put a crown upon His head\n
 Why did He slip away to a quiet place instead?\n
 Did they speak out against Him, did they dare?\n
 Did they speak out against Him, did they dare?\n

 When He rose from the dead, did they believe?\n
 When He rose from the dead, did they believe?\n
 He said, “All power is given to Me in heaven and on earth”\n
 Did they know right then and there what the power was worth?\n
 When He rose from the dead, did they believe?\n
 When He rose from the dead, did they believe?\n

    </string>
    <string name="savinggracelyrics">
If you find it in Your heart, can I be forgiven?\n
 Guess I owe You some kind of apology\n
 I’ve escaped death so many times, I know I’m only living\n
 By the saving grace that’s over me\n

 By this time I’d-a thought I would be sleeping\n
 In a pine box for all eternity\n
 My faith keeps me alive, but I still be weeping\n
 For the saving grace that’s over me\n

 Well, the death of life, then come the resurrection\n
 Wherever I am welcome is where I’ll be\n
 I put all my confidence in Him, my sole protection\n
 Is the saving grace that’s over me\n

 Well, the devil’s shining light, it can be most blinding\n
 But to search for love, that ain’t no more than vanity\n
 As I look around this world all that I’m finding\n
 Is the saving grace that’s over me\n

 The wicked know no peace and you just can’t fake it\n
 There’s only one road and it leads to Calvary\n
 It gets discouraging at times, but I know I’ll make it\n
 By the saving grace that’s over me\n


    </string>
    <string name="areyoureadylyrics">
Are you ready, are you ready?\n
 Are you ready, are you ready?\n

 Are you ready to meet Jesus?\n
 Are you where you ought to be?\n
 Will He know you when He sees you\n
 Or will He say, “Depart from Me”?\n

 Are you ready, hope you’re ready\n
 Am I ready, am I ready?\n
 Am I ready, am I ready?\n

 Am I ready to lay down my life for the brethren\n
 And to take up my cross?\n
 Have I surrendered to the will of God\n
 Or am I still acting like the boss?\n

 Am I ready, hope I’m ready\n

 When destruction cometh swiftly\n
 And there’s no time to say a fare-thee-well\n
 Have you decided whether you want to be\n
 In heaven or in hell?\n

 Are you ready, are you ready?\n

 Have you got some unfinished business?\n
 Is there something holding you back?\n
 Are you thinking for yourself\n
 Or are you following the pack?\n

 Are you ready, hope you’re ready\n
 Are you ready?\n

 Are you ready for the judgment?\n
 Are you ready for that terrible swift sword?\n
 Are you ready for Armageddon?\n
 Are you ready for the day of the Lord?\n
 \n
 Are you ready, I hope you’re ready\n


    </string>









</resources>