<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="shotoflovelyrics">I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 Don’t need a shot of heroin to kill my disease\n
 Don’t need a shot of turpentine, only bring me to my knees\n
 Don’t need a shot of codeine to help me to repent\n
 Don’t need a shot of whiskey, help me be president\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 Doctor, can you hear me? I need some Medicaid\n
 I seen the kingdoms of the world and it’s makin’ me feel afraid\n
 What I got ain’t painful, it’s just bound to kill me dead\n
 Like the men that followed Jesus when they put a price upon His head\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 I don’t need no alibi when I’m spending time with you\n
 I’ve heard all of them rumors and you have heard ’em too\n
 Don’t show me no picture show or give me no book to read\n
 It don’t satisfy the hurt inside nor the habit that it feeds\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 Why would I want to take your life?\n
 You’ve only murdered my father, raped his wife\n
 Tattooed my babies with a poison pen\n
 Mocked my God, humiliated my friends\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 Don’t wanna be with nobody tonight\n
 Veronica not around nowhere, Mavis just ain’t right\n
 There’s a man that hates me and he’s swift, smooth and near\n
 Am I supposed to set back and wait until he’s here?\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 What makes the wind wanna blow tonight?\n
 Don’t even feel like crossing the street and my car ain’t actin’ right\n
 Called home, everybody seemed to have moved away\n
 My conscience is beginning to bother me today\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n

 I need a shot of love, I need a shot of love\n
 If you’re a doctor, I need a shot of love\n

</string>
    
    <string name="heartofminelyrics">
        Heart of mine be still\n
 You can play with fire but you’ll get the bill\n
 Don’t let her know\n
 Don’t let her know that you love her\n
 Don’t be a fool, don’t be blind\n
 Heart of mine\n

 Heart of mine go back home\n
 You got no reason to wander, you got no reason to roam\n
 Don’t let her see\n
 Don’t let her see that you need her\n
 Don’t put yourself over the line\n
 Heart of mine\n

 Heart of mine go back where you been\n
 It’ll only be trouble for you if you let her in\n
 Don’t let her hear\n
 Don’t let her hear you want her\n
 Don’t let her think you think she’s fine\n
 Heart of mine\n

 Heart of mine you know that she’ll never be true\n
 She’ll only give to others the love that she’s gotten from you\n
 Don’t let her know\n
 Don’t let her know where you’re going\n
 Don’t untie the ties that bind\n
 Heart of mine\n

 Heart of mine so malicious and so full of guile\n
 Give you an inch and you’ll take a mile\n
 Don’t let yourself fall\n
 Don’t let yourself stumble\n
 If you can’t do the time, don’t do the crime\n
 Heart of mine\n


    </string>
    
    
    
    
    
    <string name="propertyofjesuslyrics">
        Go ahead and talk about him because he makes you doubt\n
 Because he has denied himself the things that you can’t live without\n
 Laugh at him behind his back just like the others do\n
 Remind him of what he used to be when he comes walkin’ through\n

 He’s the property of Jesus\n
 Resent him to the bone\n
 You got something better\n
 You’ve got a heart of stone\n

 Stop your conversation when he passes on the street\n
 Hope he falls upon himself, oh, won’t that be sweet\n
 Because he can’t be exploited by superstition anymore\n
 Because he can’t be bribed or bought by the things that you adore\n

 He’s the property of Jesus\n
 Resent him to the bone\n
 You got something better\n
 You’ve got a heart of stone\n

 When the whip that’s keeping you in line doesn’t make him jump\n
 Say he’s hard-of-hearin’, say that he’s a chump\n
 Say he’s out of step with reality as you try to test his nerve\n
 Because he doesn’t pay no tribute to the king that you serve\n

 He’s the property of Jesus\n
 Resent him to the bone\n
 You got something better\n
 You’ve got a heart of stone\n

 Say that he’s a loser ’cause he got no common sense\n
 Because he don’t increase his worth at someone else’s expense\n
 Because he’s not afraid of trying, ’cause he don’t look at you and smile\n
 ’Cause he doesn’t tell you jokes or fairy tales, say he’s got no style\n

 He’s the property of Jesus\n
 Resent him to the bone\n
 You got something better\n
 You’ve got a heart of stone\n
 You can laugh at salvation, you can play Olympic games\n
 You think that when you rest at last you’ll go back from where you came\n
 But you’ve picked up quite a story and you’ve changed since the womb\n
 What happened to the real you, you’ve been captured but by whom?\n

 He’s the property of Jesus\n
 Resent him to the bone\n
 You got something better\n
 You’ve got a heart of stone\n



    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="lennybrucelyrics">
Lenny Bruce is dead but his ghost lives on and on\n
 Never did get any Golden Globe award, never made it to Synanon\n
 He was an outlaw, that’s for sure\n
 More of an outlaw than you ever were\n
 Lenny Bruce is gone but his spirit’s livin’ on and on\n
 Maybe he had some problems, maybe some things that he couldn’t work out\n
 But he sure was funny and he sure told the truth and he knew what he was talkin’ about\n
 Never robbed any churches nor cut off any babies’ heads\n
 He just took the folks in high places and he shined a light in their beds\n
 He’s on some other shore, he didn’t wanna live anymore\n

 Lenny Bruce is dead but he didn’t commit any crime\n
 He just had the insight to rip off the lid before its time\n
 I rode with him in a taxi once\n
 Only for a mile and a half, seemed like it took a couple of months\n
 Lenny Bruce moved on and like the ones that killed him, gone\n

 They said that he was sick ’cause he didn’t play by the rules\n
 He just showed the wise men of his day to be nothing more than fools\n
 They stamped him and they labeled him like they do with pants and shirts\n
 He fought a war on a battlefield where every victory hurts\n
 Lenny Bruce was bad, he was the brother that you never had\n


    </string>


    <string name="watereddownlovelyrics">
Love that’s pure hopes all things\n
 Believes all things, won’t pull no strings\n
 Won’t sneak up into your room, tall, dark and handsome\n
 Capture your heart and hold it for ransom\n

 You don’t want a love that’s pure\n
 You wanna drown love\n
 You want a watered-down love\n

 Love that’s pure, it don’t make no false claims\n
 Intercedes for you ’stead of casting you blame\n
 Will not deceive you or lead you into transgression\n
 Won’t write it up and make you sign a false confession\n

 You don’t want a love that’s pure\n
 You wanna drown love\n
 You want a watered-down love\n

 Love that’s pure won’t lead you astray\n
 Won’t hold you back, won’t mess up your day\n
 Won’t pervert you, corrupt you with stupid wishes\n
 It don’t make you envious, it don’t make you suspicious\n

 You don’t want a love that’s pure\n
 You wanna drown love\n
 You want a watered-down love\n

 Love that’s pure ain’t no accident\n
 Always on time, is always content\n
 An eternal flame, quietly burning\n
 Never needs to be proud, restlessly yearning\n

 You don’t want a love that’s pure\n
 You wanna drown love\n
 You want a watered-down love\n



    </string>
    
    
    <string name="thegroomsstillwaitinglyrics">
Prayed in the ghetto with my face in the cement\n
 Heard the last moan of a boxer, seen the massacre of the innocent \n
 Felt around for the light switch, became nauseated\n
 She was walking down the hallway while the walls deteriorated\n

 West of the Jordan, east of the Rock of Gibraltar \n
 I see the turning of the page\n
 Curtain risin’ on a new age\n
 See the groom still waitin’ at the altar\n

 Try to be pure at heart, they arrest you for robbery\n
 Mistake your shyness for aloofness, your silence for snobbery \n
 Got the message this morning, the one that was sent to me \n
 About the madness of becomin’ what one was never meant to be\n

 West of the Jordan, east of the Rock of Gibraltar \n
 I see the burning of the stage\n
 Curtain risin’ on a new age\n
 See the groom still waitin’ at the altar\n

 Don’t know what I can say\n
        about Claudette that wouldn’t come back to haunt me\n
        Finally had to give her up ’bout the time she began to want me\n
 But I know God has mercy on them who are slandered and humiliated\n
 I’d a-done anything for that woman if she didn’t make me feel so obligated\n

 West of the Jordan, east of the Rock of Gibraltar \n
 I see the burning of the cage\n
 Curtain risin’ on a new stage\n
 See the groom still waitin’ at the altar\n

 Put your hand on my head, baby, do I have a temperature?\n
 I see people who are supposed to know better \n
        standin’ around like furniture\n
        There’s a wall between you and what you want and you got to leap it\n
 Tonight you got the power to take it, tomorrow you won’t have the power to keep it\n

 West of the Jordan, east of the Rock of Gibraltar \n
 I see the burning of the stage\n
 Curtain risin’ on a new age\n
 See the groom still waitin’ at the altar\n

 Cities on fire, phones out of order\n
 They’re killing nuns and soldiers, there’s fighting on the border\n
 What can I say about Claudette? Ain’t seen her since January\n
 She could be respectfully married or running a whorehouse in Buenos Aires\n

 West of the Jordan, east of the Rock of Gibraltar \n
 I see the burning of the stage\n
 Curtain risin’ on a new age\n
 See the groom still waitin’ at the altar\n



    </string>
    
    <string name="deadmanlyrics">

Uttering idle words from a reprobate mind\n
 Clinging to strange promises, dying on the vine\n
 Never bein’ able to separate the good from the bad\n
 Ooh, I can’t stand it, I can’t stand it\n
 It’s makin’ me feel so sad\n

 Dead man, dead man\n
 When will you arise?\n
 Cobwebs in your mind\n
 Dust upon your eyes\n

 Satan got you by the heel, there’s a bird’s nest in your hair\n
 Do you have any faith at all? Do you have any love to share?\n
 The way that you hold your head, cursin’ God with every move\n
 Ooh, I can’t stand it, I can’t stand it\n
 What are you tryin’ to prove?\n

 Dead man, dead man\n
 When will you arise?\n
 Cobwebs in your mind\n
 Dust upon your eyes\n

 The glamour and the bright lights and the politics of sin\n
 The ghetto that you build for me is the one you end up in\n
 The race of the engine that overrules your heart\n
 Ooh, I can’t stand it, I can’t stand it\n
 Pretending that you’re so smart\n

 Dead man, dead man\n
 When will you arise?\n
 Cobwebs in your mind\n
 Dust upon your eyes\n

 What are you tryin’ to overpower me with, the doctrine or the gun?\n
 My back is already to the wall, where can I run?\n
 The tuxedo that you’re wearin’, the flower in your lapel\n
 Ooh, I can’t stand it, I can’t stand it\n
 You wanna take me down to hell\n

 Dead man, dead man\n
 When will you arise?\n
 Cobwebs in your mind\n
 Dust upon your eyes\n


    </string>
    
   <string name="inthesummetimelyrics">
 I was in your presence \n
    for an hour or so\n
 Or was it a day? I truly don’t know\n
 Where the sun never set, \n
    where the trees hung low\n
 By that soft and shining sea\n
 Did you respect me for what I did\n
 Or for what I didn’t do, \n
    or for keeping it hid?\n
 Did I lose my mind when I tried to get rid\n
 Of everything you see?\n

 In the summertime, ah in the summertime\n
 In the summertime, when you were with me\n

 I got the heart and you got the blood\n
 We cut through iron\n
    and we cut through mud\n
 Then came the warnin’ \n
    that was before the flood\n
 That set everybody free\n
 Fools they made a mock of sin\n
 Our loyalty they tried to win\n
 But you were closer to me \n
    than my next of kin\n
 When they didn’t want to know or see\n

 In the summertime, ah in the summertime\n
 In the summertime when you were with me\n

 Strangers, they meddled in our affairs\n
 Poverty and shame was theirs\n
 But all that sufferin’ was not to be compared\n
 With the glory that is to be\n
 And I’m still carrying the gift you gave\n
 It’s a part of me now, \n
    it’s been cherished and saved\n
 It’ll be with me unto the grave\n
 And then unto eternity\n

 In the summertime, ah in the summertime\n
 In the summertime when you were with me\n


   </string>
    <string name="troublelyrics">
Trouble in the city, trouble in the farm\n
 You got your rabbit’s foot, you got your good-luck charm\n
 But they can’t help you none when there’s trouble\n

 Trouble\n
 Trouble, trouble, trouble\n
 Nothin’ but trouble\n

 Trouble in the water, trouble in the air\n
 Go all the way to the other side of the world, you’ll find trouble there\n
 Revolution even ain’t no solution for trouble\n

 Trouble\n
 Trouble, trouble, trouble\n
 Nothin’ but trouble\n

 Drought and starvation, packaging of the soul\n
 Persecution, execution, governments out of control\n
 You can see the writing on the wall inviting trouble\n

 Trouble\n
 Trouble, trouble, trouble\n
 Nothin’ but trouble\n

 Put your ear to the train tracks, put your ear to the ground\n
 You ever feel like you’re never alone even when there’s nobody else around?\n
 Since the beginning of the universe man’s been cursed by trouble\n

 Trouble\n
 Trouble, trouble, trouble\n
 Nothin’ but trouble\n

 Nightclubs of the broken-hearted, stadiums of the damned\n
 Legislature, perverted nature, doors that are rudely slammed\n
 Look into infinity, all you see is trouble\n

 Trouble\n
 Trouble, trouble, trouble\n
 Nothin’ but trouble\n



    </string>
    
    <string name="everygrainofsandlyrics">

In the time of my confession, in the hour of my deepest need\n
 When the pool of tears beneath my feet flood every newborn seed\n
 There’s a dyin’ voice within me reaching out somewhere\n
 Toiling in the danger and in the morals of despair\n

 Don’t have the inclination to look back on any mistake\n
 Like Cain, I now behold this chain of events that I must break\n
 In the fury of the moment I can see the Master’s hand\n
 In every leaf that trembles, in every grain of sand\n

 Oh, the flowers of indulgence and the weeds of yesteryear\n
 Like criminals, they have choked the breath of conscience and good cheer\n
 The sun beat down upon the steps of time to light the way\n
 To ease the pain of idleness and the memory of decay\n

 I gaze into the doorway of temptation’s angry flame\n
 And every time I pass that way I always hear my name\n
 Then onward in my journey I come to understand\n
 That every hair is numbered like every grain of sand\n

 I have gone from rags to riches in the sorrow of the night\n
 In the violence of a summer’s dream, in the chill of a wintry light\n
 In the bitter dance of loneliness fading into space\n
 In the broken mirror of innocence on each forgotten face\n

 I hear the ancient footsteps like the motion of the sea\n
 Sometimes I turn, there’s someone there, other times it’s only me\n
 I am hanging in the balance of the reality of man\n
 Like every sparrow falling, like every grain of sand\n


    </string>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
</resources>