<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
   <string name="changingoftheguardlyrics">
       Sixteen years\n
 Sixteen banners united over the field\n
 Where the good shepherd grieves\n
 Desperate men, desperate women divided\n
 Spreading their wings ’neath the falling leaves\n

 Fortune calls\n
 I stepped forth from the shadows, to the marketplace\n
 Merchants and thieves, hungry for power, my last deal gone down\n
 She’s smelling sweet like the meadows where she was born\n
 On midsummer’s eve, near the tower\n

 The cold-blooded moon\n
 The captain waits above the celebration\n
 Sending his thoughts to a beloved maid\n
 Whose ebony face is beyond communication\n
 The captain is down but still believing that his love will be repaid\n

 They shaved her head\n
 She was torn between Jupiter and Apollo\n
 A messenger arrived with a black nightingale\n
 I seen her on the stairs and I couldn’t help but follow\n
 Follow her down past the fountain where they lifted her veil\n

 I stumbled to my feet\n
 I rode past destruction in the ditches\n
 With the stitches still mending ’neath a heart-shaped tattoo\n
 Renegade priests and treacherous young witches\n
 Were handing out the flowers that I’d given to you\n

 The palace of mirrors\n
 Where dog soldiers are reflected\n
 The endless road and the wailing of chimes\n
 The empty rooms where her memory is protected\n
 Where the angels’ voices whisper to the souls of previous times\n

 She wakes him up\n
 Forty-eight hours later, the sun is breaking\n
 Near broken chains, mountain laurel and rolling rocks\n
 She’s begging to know what measures he now will be taking\n
 He’s pulling her down and she’s clutching on to his long golden locks\n

 Gentlemen, he said\n
 I don’t need your organization, I’ve shined your shoes\n
 I’ve moved your mountains and marked your cards\n
 But Eden is burning, either brace yourself for elimination\n
 Or else your hearts must have the courage for the changing of the guards\n

 Peace will come\n
 With tranquillity and splendor on the wheels of fire\n
 But will bring us no reward when her false idols fall\n
 And cruel death surrenders with its pale ghost retreating\n
 Between the King and the Queen of Swords\n

   </string> 
    <string name="newponylyrics">
        Once I had a pony, her name was Lucifer\n
 I had a pony, her name was Lucifer\n
 She broke her leg and she needed shooting\n
 I swear it hurt me more than it could ever have hurted her\n

 Sometimes I wonder what’s going on in the mind of Miss X\n
 Sometimes I wonder what’s going on in the mind of Miss X\n
 You know she got such a sweet disposition\n
 I never know what the poor girl’s gonna do to me next\n

 I got a new pony, she knows how to fox-trot, lope and pace\n
 Well, I got a new pony, she knows how to fox-trot, lope and pace\n
 She got great big hind legs\n
 And long black shaggy hair above her face\n

 Well now, it was early in the mornin’, I seen your shadow in the door\n
 It was early in the mornin’, I seen your shadow in the door\n
 Now, I don’t have to ask nobody\n
 I know what you come here for\n

 They say you’re usin’ voodoo, your feet walk by themselves\n
 They say you’re usin’ voodoo, I seen your feet walk by themselves\n
 Oh, baby, that god you been prayin’ to\n
 Is gonna give ya back what you’re wishin’ on someone else\n

 Come over here pony, I, I wanna climb up one time on you\n
 Come over here pony, I, I wanna climb up one time on you\n
 Well, you’re so bad and nasty\n
 But I love you, yes I do\n


    </string>
    <string name="notimetothinklyrics">
        In death, you face life with a child and a wife\n
 Who sleep-walks through your dreams into walls\n
 You’re a soldier of mercy,\n
     you’re cold and you curse\n
 “He who cannot be trusted must fall”\n

 Loneliness, tenderness, \n
     high society, notoriety\n
 You fight for the throne and you travel alone\n
 Unknown as you slowly sink\n
 And there’s no time to think\n

 In the Federal City you been blown and shown pity\n
 In secret, for pieces of change\n
 The empress attracts you but oppression distracts you\n
 And it makes you feel violent and strange\n

 Memory, ecstasy, tyranny, hypocrisy\n
 Betrayed by a kiss on a cool night of bliss\n
 In the valley of the missing link\n
 And you have no time to think\n

 Judges will haunt you, \n
     the country priestess will want you\n
 Her worst is better than best\n
 I’ve seen all these decoys \n
     through a set of deep turquoise eyes\n
 And I feel so depressed\n

 China doll, alcohol, duality, mortality\n
 Mercury rules you and destiny fools you\n
 Like the plague, with a dangerous wink\n
 And there’s no time to think\n

 Your conscience betrayed you \n
     when some tyrant waylaid you\n
 Where the lion lies down with the lamb\n
 I’d have paid off the traitor and killed him much later\n
 But that’s just the way that I am\n

 Paradise, sacrifice, mortality, reality\n
 But the magician is quicker and his game\n
 Is much thicker than blood and blacker than ink\n
 And there’s no time to think\n

 Anger and jealousy’s all that he sells us\n
 He’s content when you’re under his thumb\n
 Madmen oppose him, but your kindness throws him\n
 To survive it you play deaf and dumb\n

 Equality, liberty, humility, simplicity\n
 You glance through the mirror \n
     and there’s eyes staring clear\n
 At the back of your head as you drink\n
 And there’s no time to think\n

 Warlords of sorrow and queens of tomorrow\n
 Will offer their heads for a prayer\n
 You can’t find no salvation, you have no expectations\n
 Anytime, anyplace, anywhere\n

 Mercury, gravity, nobility, humility\n
 You know you can’t keep her and the water gets deeper\n
 That is leading you onto the brink\n
 But there’s no time to think\n

 You’ve murdered your vanity, buried your sanity\n
 For pleasure you must now resist\n
 Lovers obey you but they cannot sway you\n
 They’re not even sure you exist\n

 Socialism, hypnotism, patriotism, materialism\n
 Fools making laws for the breaking of jaws\n
 And the sound of the keys as they clink\n
 But there’s no time to think\n

 The bridge that you travel on goes to the Babylon girl\n
 With the rose in her hair\n
 Starlight in the East and you’re finally released\n
 You’re stranded but with nothing to share\n

 Loyalty, unity, epitome, rigidity\n
 You turn around for one real last glimpse of Camille\n
 ’Neath the moon shinin’ bloody and pink\n
 And there’s no time to think\n

 Bullets can harm you and death can disarm you\n
 But no, you will not be deceived\n
 Stripped of all virtue as you crawl through the dirt\n
 You can give but you cannot receive\n

 No time to choose when the truth must die\n
 No time to lose or say goodbye\n
 No time to prepare for the victim that’s there\n
 No time to suffer or blink\n
 And no time to think\n


    </string>
    
    <string name="babystopcryinglyrics">
        You been down to the bottom with a bad man, babe\n
 But you’re back where you belong\n
 Go get me my pistol, babe\n
 Honey, I can’t tell right from wrong\n

 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying\n
 You know, I know, the sun will always shine\n
 So baby, please stop crying ’cause it’s tearing up my mind\n
 Go down to the river, babe\n
 Honey, I will meet you there\n
 Go down to the river, babe\n
 Honey, I will pay your fare\n

 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying\n
 You know, I know, the sun will always shine\n
 So baby, please stop crying ’cause it’s tearing up my mind\n

 If you’re looking for assistance, babe\n
 Or if you just want some company\n
 Or if you just want a friend you can talk to\n
 Honey, come and see about me\n

 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying\n
 You know, I know, the sun will always shine\n
 So baby, please stop crying ’cause it’s tearing up my mind\n

 You been hurt so many times\n
 And I know what you’re thinking of\n
 Well, I don’t have to be no doctor, babe\n
 To see that you’re madly in love\n

 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying, stop crying, stop crying\n
 Baby, please stop crying\n
 You know, I know, the sun will always shine\n
 So baby, please stop crying ’cause it’s tearing up my mind\n



    </string>
    
    <string name="isyourloveinvainlyrics">

        Do you love me, or are you just extending goodwill?\n
 Do you need me half as bad as you say, or are you just feeling guilt?\n
 I’ve been burned before and I know the score\n
 So you won’t hear me complain\n
 Will I be able to count on you\n
 Or is your love in vain?\n

 Are you so fast that you cannot see that I must have solitude?\n
 When I am in the darkness, why do you intrude?\n
 Do you know my world, do you know my kind\n
 Or must I explain?\n
 Will you let me be myself\n
 Or is your love in vain?\n

 Well I’ve been to the mountain and I’ve been in the wind\n
 I’ve been in and out of happiness\n
 I have dined with kings, I’ve been offered wings\n
 And I’ve never been too impressed\n

 All right, I’ll take a chance, I will fall in love with you\n
 If I’m a fool you can have the night, you can have the morning too\n
 Can you cook and sew, make flowers grow\n
 Do you understand my pain?\n
 Are you willing to risk it all\n
 Or is your love in vain?\n


    </string>
    
    <string name="senorlyrics">
        Señor, señor, do you know where we’re headin’?\n
 Lincoln County Road or Armageddon?\n
 Seems like I been down this way before\n
 Is there any truth in that, señor?\n

 Señor, señor, do you know where she is hidin’?\n
 How long are we gonna be ridin’?\n
 How long must I keep my eyes glued to the door?\n
 Will there be any comfort there, señor?\n

 There’s a wicked wind still blowin’ on that upper deck\n
 There’s an iron cross still hangin\' down from around her neck\n
 There’s a marchin’ band still playin’ in that vacant lot\n
 Where she held me in her arms one time and said, “Forget me not”\n

 Señor, señor, I can see that painted wagon\n
 I can smell the tail of the dragon\n
 Can’t stand the suspense anymore\n
 Can you tell me who to contact here, señor?\n

 Well, the last thing I remember before I stripped and kneeled\n
 Was that trainload of fools bogged down in a magnetic field\n
 A gypsy with a broken flag and a flashing ring\n
 Said, “Son, this ain’t a dream no more, it’s the real thing”\n

 Señor, señor, you know their hearts is as hard as leather\n
 Well, give me a minute, let me get it together\n
 I just gotta pick myself up off the floor\n
 I’m ready when you are, señor\n

 Señor, señor, let’s disconnect these cables\n
 Overturn these tables\n
 This place don’t make sense to me no more\n
 Can you tell me what we’re waiting for, señor?\n



    </string>
    

    <string name="truelovetendstoforgetlyrics">
I’m getting weary looking in my baby’s eyes\n
 When she’s near me she’s so hard to recognize\n
 I finally realize there’s no room for regret\n
 True love, true love, true love tends to forget\n

 Hold me, baby be near\n
 You told me that you’d be sincere\n
 Every day of the year’s like playin’ Russian roulette\n
 True love, true love, true love tends to forget\n

 I was lyin’ down in the reeds without any oxygen\n
 I saw you in the wilderness among the men\n
 Saw you drift into infinity and come back again\n
 All you got to do is wait and I’ll tell you when\n

 You’re a tearjerker, baby, but I’m under your spell\n
 You’re a hard worker, baby, and I know you well\n
 But this weekend in hell is making me sweat\n
 True love, true love, true love tends to forget\n

 I was lyin’ down in the reeds without any oxygen\n
 I saw you in the wilderness among the men\n
 Saw you drift into infinity and come back again\n
 All you got to do is wait and I’ll tell you when\n

 You belong to me, baby, without any doubt\n
 Don’t forsake me, baby, don’t sell me out\n
 Don’t keep me knockin’ about from Mexico to Tibet\n
 True love, true love, true love tends to forget\n


    </string>


    <string name="webettertalkthisoverlyrics">
        I think we better talk this over\n
 Maybe when we both get sober\n
 You’ll understand I’m only a man\n
 Doin’ the best that I can\n

 This situation can only get rougher\n
 Why should we needlessly suffer?\n
 Let’s call it a day, go our own different ways\n
 Before we decay\n

 You don’t have to be afraid of looking into my face\n
 We’ve done nothing to each other time will not erase\n

 I feel displaced, I got a low-down feeling\n
 You been two-faced, you been double-dealing\n
 I took a chance, got caught in the trance\n
 Of a downhill dance\n

 Oh, child, why you wanna hurt me?\n
 I’m exiled, you can’t convert me\n
 I’m lost in the haze of your delicate ways\n
 With both eyes glazed\n

 You don’t have to yearn for love, you don’t have to be alone\n
 Somewheres in this universe there’s a place that you can call home\n

 I guess I’ll be leaving tomorrow\n
 If I have to beg, steal or borrow\n
 It’d be great to cross paths in a day and a half\n
 Look at each other and laugh\n

 But I don’t think it’s liable to happen\n
 Like the sound of one hand clappin’\n
 The vows that we kept are now broken and swept\n
 ’Neath the bed where we slept\n

 Don’t think of me and fantasize on what we never had\n
 Be grateful for what we’ve shared together and be glad\n
 Why should we go on watching each other through a telescope?\n
 Eventually we’ll hang ourselves on all this tangled rope\n

 Oh, babe, time for a new transition\n
 I wish I was a magician\n
 I would wave a wand and tie back the bond\n
 That we’ve both gone beyond\n



    </string>

    <string name="whereareyoutonightlyrics">

        There’s a long-distance train rolling through the rain\n
 Tears on the letter I write\n
 There’s a woman I long to touch and I miss her so much\n
 But she’s drifting like a satellite\n

 There’s a neon light ablaze in this green smoky haze\n
 Laughter down on Elizabeth Street\n
 And a lonesome bell tone in that valley of stone\n
 Where she bathed in a stream of pure heat\n

 Her father would emphasize you got to be more than streetwise\n
 But he practiced what he preached from the heart\n
 A full-blooded Cherokee, he predicted to me\n
 The time and the place that the trouble would start\n

 There’s a babe in the arms of a woman in a rage\n
 And a longtime golden-haired stripper onstage\n
 And she winds back the clock and she turns back the page\n
 Of a book that no one can write\n
 Oh, where are you tonight?\n

 The truth was obscure, too profound and too pure\n
 To live it you have to explode\n
 In that last hour of need, we entirely agreed\n
 Sacrifice was the code of the road\n

 I left town at dawn, with Marcel and St. John\n
 Strong men belittled by doubt\n
 I couldn’t tell her what my private thoughts were\n
 But she had some way of finding them out\n

 He took dead-center aim but he missed just the same\n
 She was waiting, putting flowers on the shelf\n
 She could feel my despair as I climbed up her hair\n
 And discovered her invisible self\n

 There’s a lion in the road, there’s a demon escaped\n
 There’s a million dreams gone, there’s a landscape being raped\n
 As her beauty fades and I watch her undrape\n
 I won’t but then again, maybe I might\n
 Oh, if I could just find you tonight\n

 I fought with my twin, that enemy within\n
 ’Til both of us fell by the way\n
 Horseplay and disease is killing me by degrees\n
 While the law looks the other way\n

 Your partners in crime hit me up for nickels and dimes\n
 The guy you were lovin’ couldn’t stay clean\n
 It felt outa place, my foot in his face\n
 But he should-a stayed where his money was green\n

 I bit into the root of forbidden fruit\n
 With the juice running down my leg\n
 Then I dealt with your boss, who’d never known about loss\n
 And who always was too proud to beg\n

 There’s a white diamond gloom on the dark side of this room\n
 And a pathway that leads up to the stars\n
 If you don’t believe there’s a price for this sweet paradise\n
 Remind me to show you the scars\n

 There’s a new day at dawn and I’ve finally arrived\n
 If I’m there in the morning, baby, you’ll know I’ve survived\n
 I can’t believe it, I can’t believe I’m alive\n
 But without you it just doesn’t seem right\n
 Oh, where are you tonight?\n



    </string>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
</resources>