<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="duquesnewhistlelyrics">
        Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like it’s gonna sweep my world away\n
 I’m gonna stop in Carbondale and keep on going\n
 That Duquesne train gonna ride me night and day\n

 You say I’m a gambler, you say I’m a pimp \n
 But I ain’t neither one\n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Sound like it’s on a final run\n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like she never blowed before\n
 Blue light blinkin’, red light glowin’ \n
 Blowin’ like she’s at my chamber door\n

 You smiling through the fence at me\n
 Just like you always smiled before\n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like she ain’t gonna blow no more\n

 Can’t you hear that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like the sky’s gonna blow apart\n
 You’re the only thing alive that keeps me goin’\n
 You’re like a time bomb in my heart\n

 I can hear a sweet voice gently calling\n
 Must be the Mother of our Lord\n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like my woman’s on board\n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like it’s gonna blow my blues away\n
 You ole rascal, I know exactly where you’re goin’\n
 I’ll lead you there myself at the break of day\n

 I wake up every morning with that woman in my bed \n
 Everybody telling me she’s gone to my head\n


 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like it’s gonna kill me dead\n

 Can’t you hear that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ through another no-good town \n
 The lights of my native land are glowin’\n
 I wonder if they’ll know me next time around \n

 I wonder if that old oak tree’s still standing\n
 That old oak tree, the one we used to climb \n

 Listen to that Duquesne whistle blowin’\n
 Blowin’ like she’s blowin’ right on time \n


    </string>

    <string name="soonaftermidnightlyrics">
I’m searching for phrases to sing your praises\n
 I need to tell someone\n
 It’s soon after midnight and my day has just begun\n

 A gal named Honey took my money\n
 She was passing by\n
 It’s soon after midnight and the moon is in my eye\n

 My heart is cheerful, it’s never fearful\n
 I been down on the killing floors\n
 I’m in no great hurry, I’m not afraid of your fury\n
 I\'ve faced stronger walls than yours\n

 Charlotte’s a harlot, dresses in scarlet\n
 Mary dresses in green\n
 It’s soon after midnight and I’ve got a date with a fairy queen\n

 They chirp and they chatter, what does it matter\n
 They’re lying there dying in their blood\n
 Two Timing Slim, who’s ever heard of him?\n
 I’ll drag his corpse through the mud\n

 It’s now or never, more than ever\n
 When I met you I didn’t think you would do\n
 It’s soon after midnight and I don’t want nobody but you\n



    </string>
    <string name="narrowwaylyrics">

I’m gonna walk across the desert ‘til I’m in my right mind\n
 I won’t even think about what I left behind\n
 Nothin\' back there anyway I can call my own\n
 Go back home, leave me alone\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 Ever since the British burned the white house down\n
 There’s a bleeding wound in the heart of town\n
 I saw you drinking from an empty cup\n
 I saw you buried and I saw you dug up\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 Look down angel, from the skies\n
 Help my weary soul to rise\n
 I kissed your cheek, I dragged your plow\n
 You broke my heart. I was your friend ‘til now\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 In the courtyard of the golden sun\n
 You stand and fight or you break and run\n
 You went and lost your lovely head\n
 For a drink of wine and a crust of bread\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 We looted and we plundered on distant shores\n
 Why is my share not equal to yours?\n
 Your father left you, your mother too\n
 Even death has washed his hands of you\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 This is hard country to stay alive in\n
 Blades are everywhere and they’re breaking my skin\n
 I’m armed to the hilt and I’m struggling hard \n
 You won’t get out of here unscarred\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 You got too many lovers waiting at the wall\n
 If I had a thousand tongues I couldn’t count them all\n
 Yesterday I could have thrown them all in the sea\n
 Today, even one may be too much for me\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 Cake walking baby, you can do no wrong \n
 Put your arms around me where they belong\n
 I want to take you on a roller coaster ride\n
 Lay my hands all over you, tie you to my side\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 I got a heavy stacked woman with a smile on her face\n
 And she has crowned my soul with grace\n
 I’m still hurting from an arrow that pierced my chest\n
 I’m gonna have to take my head and bury it between your breasts\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 Been dark all night, but now it’s dawn\n
 The moving finger is moving on\n
 You can guard me while I sleep\n
 Kiss away the tears I weep\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

 I love women and she loves men\n
 We’ve been to the West and we going back again\n
 I heard a voice at the dusk of day\n
 Saying, “Be gentle brother, be gentle and pray”\n

 It’s a long road, it’s a long and narrow way\n
 If I can’t work up to you\n
 You’ll have to work down to me someday\n

    </string>
    <string name="longandwastedyearslyrics">

It’s been such a long, long time \n
 Since we loved each other and our hearts were true\n
 One time, for one brief day \n
 I was the man for you\n

 Last night I heard you talking in your sleep\n
 Saying things you shouldn’t say\n
 Oh, baby \n
 You just might have to go to jail some day\n

 Is there a place we can go? \n
 Is there anybody we can see?\n
 Maybe what\'s right for you\n
 Isn\'t really right for me\n

 I ain’t seen my family in twenty years\n
 That ain’t easy to understand\n
 They may be dead by now\n
 I lost track of them after they lost their land\n

 Shake it up baby, twist and shout\n
 You tell me what it\'s all about\n
 What you doing out in the sun anyway?\n
 Don’t you know the sun can burn your brains right out?\n

 My enemy slammed into the earth\n
 I don’t know what he was worth\n
 But he lost it all, everything and more \n
 What a blithering fool he took me for\n

 I wear dark glasses to cover my eyes\n
 There’re secrets in them I can’t disguise\n
 Come back, baby\n
 If I hurt your feelings, I apologize\n

 Two trains running side by side \n
 Forty miles wide down the Eastern line\n
 You don’t have to go, I just came to you \n
 Because you’re a friend of mine\n

 I think when my back was turned \n
 The whole world behind me burned\n
 Maybe today, if not today, maybe tomorrow\n
 Maybe there\’ll be a limit on all my sorrow\n

 We cried on a cold and frosty morn’\n
 We cried because our souls were torn\n
 So much for tears\n
 So much for those long and wasted years.\n


    </string>
    <string name="payinbloodlyrics">
Well I`m grinding my life away, steady and sure\n
 Nothing more wretched than what I must endure\n
 I`m drenched in the light that shines from the sun\n
 I could stone you to death\n
     for the wrongs that you done\n

 Sooner or later you`ll make a mistake\n
 I`ll put you in a chain \n
     that you never can break \n
 Legs and arms and body and bone\n
 I pay in blood, but not my own\n

 Night after night, day after day\n
 They strip your useless hopes away\n
 The more I take, the more I give\n
 The more I die, the more I live\n

 I got something in my pocket \n
     make your eyeballs swim \n
 I got dogs that could tear you \n
     limb to limb\n
 I`m circling around in the southern zone\n
 I pay in blood, but not my own \n

 Another political pumping out his piss\n
 Another ragged beggar blowin’ ya a kiss\n
 Life is short and it don’t last long\n
 They`ll hang you in the morning and sing ya a song\n

 Someone must have slipped a drug in your wine \n
 You gulped it down and you lost your mind\n
 My head so hard, it must be made of stone\n
 I pay in blood, but not my own\n

 How I made it back home nobody knows\n
 Or how I survived so many blows\n
 I been through hell, what good did it do?\n
 My conscience is clear, what about you?\n

 I’ll give you justice, \n
     I’ll fatten your purse\n
 Show me your moral virtues first\n
 Hear me holler hear me moan \n
 I pay in blood but not my own\n

 You bit your lover in the bed, \n
 Come here I`ll break your lousy head \n
 Our nation must be saved and freed\n
 You been accused of murder, \n
     how do you plead?\n

 This is how I spend my days\n
 I came to bury not to praise\n
 I`ll drink my fill and sleep alone\n
 I pay in blood, but not my own\n



    </string>
    <string name="scarlettownlyrics">

In Scarlet Town where I was born\n
 There\’s ivy leaf and silver thorn\n
 The streets have names you can\’t pronounce\n
 Gold is down to a quarter of an ounce\n

 The music starts and the people sway\n
 Everybody says, are you going my way?\n
 Uncle Tom still working for Uncle Bill\n
 Scarlet town is under the hill\n

 Scarlet Town in the month of May\n
 Sweet William on his deathbed lay\n
 Mistress Mary by the side of the bed\n
 Kissing his face, heaping prayers on his head\n

 So brave, so true, so gentle is he\n
 I\’ll weep for him as he\’d weep for me\n
 Little Boy Blue come blow your horn\n
 In Scarlet Town where I was born\n

 Scarlet Town in the hot noon hours\n
 There\’s palm leaf shadows and scattered flowers\n
 Beggars crouching at the gate\n
 Help comes but it comes too late\n

 On marble slabs and in fields of stone\n
 You make your humble wishes known\n
 I touched the garment but the hem was torn\n
 In Scarlet Town where I was born\n

 In Scarlet Town the end is near\n
 The seven wonders of the world are here\n
 The evil and the good living side by side\n
 All human forms seem glorified\n

 Put your heart on a platter and see who’ll bite\n
 See who’ll hold you and kiss you good night\n
 There\’s walnut groves and maple wood\n
 In Scarlet town crying won’t do you no good\n

 In Scarlet Town you fight your father’s foes\n
 Up on the hill a chilly wind blows\n
 You fight \‘em on high and you fight ‘em down in\n
 You fight \‘em with whisky, morphine and gin\n

 You got legs that can drive men mad\n
 A lot of things we didn\’t do that I wish we had\n
 In Scarlet Town the sky is clear\n
 You\'ll wish to God that you stayed right here\n

 Set \‘em up Joe, play Walking The Floor\n
 Play it for my flat chested junky whore\n
 I’m staying up late and I’m making amends\n
 While the smile of heaven descends\n
 If love is a sin than beauty is a crime\n
 All things are beautiful in their time\n
 The black and the white, the yellow and the brown\n
 It’s all right there for ya in Scarlet Town\n


    </string>
    <string name="earlyromankindslyrics">
        All the early Roman Kings in their sharkskin suits\n
 Bowties and buttons, high top boots\n
 Driving the spikes in, blazing the rails\n
 Nailed in their coffins in top hats and tails\n
 Fly away little bird, fly away, flap your wings\n
 Fly by night like the early Roman Kings\n

 All the early Roman Kings in the early, early morn’\n
 Coming down the mountain, distributing the corn\n
 Speeding through the forest, racing down the track\n
 You try to get away, they drag you back\n
 Tomorrow is Friday, we\’ll see what it brings\n
 Everybody’s talking ‘bout the early Roman Kings\n

 They\’re peddlers and they\’re meddlers, they buy and they sell\n
 They destroyed your city, they\’ll destroy you as well\n
 They\’re lecherous and treacherous, hell bent for leather \n
 Each of them bigger than all men put together\n
 Sluggers and muggers wearing fancy gold rings\n
 All the women going crazy for the early Roman Kings\n

 I\'ll dress up your wounds with a blood clotted rag\n
 I ain\’t afraid to make love to a bitch or a hag \n
 If you see me coming and you’re standing there\n
 Wave your handkerchief in the air\n
 I ain\’t dead yet, my bell still rings\n
 I keep my fingers crossed like the early Roman Kings\n

 I\'ll strip you of life, strip you of breath\n
 Ship you down to the house of death\n
 One day you will ask for me\n
 There\’ll be no one else that you\’ll want to see\n
 Bring down my fiddle, tune up my strings\n
 Gonna break it wide open like the early Roman Kings\n

 I was up on black mountain the day Detroit fell\n
 They killed them all off and they sent them to hell\n
 Ding Dong Daddy, you\’re coming up short\n
 Gonna put you on trial in a Sicilian court\n
 I\’ve had my fun, I\’ve had my flings\n
 Gonna shake \‘em all down like the early Roman Kings\n

    </string>
    <string name="tinangellyrics">
It was late last night when the boss came home\n
 To a deserted mansion and a desolate throne\n
 Servant said, “Boss, the lady\’s gone\n
 She left this morning just \‘fore dawn.”\n
 \“You got something to tell me, tell it to me, man. \n
 Come to the point as straight as you can.\”\n
 \“Old Henry Lee, chief of the clan, \n
 Came riding through the woods and took her by the hand.\” \n
 The boss he laid back flat on his bed\n
 He cursed the heat and he clutched his head\n
 He pondered the future of his fate \n
 To wait another day would be far too late\n
 \"Go fetch me my coat and my tie
 And the cheapest labor that money can buy
 Saddle me up my buckskin mare
 If you see me go by, put up a prayer.\"
 Well, they rode all night and they rode all day\n
 Eastward long on the broad highway \n
 His spirit was tired and his vision was bent\n
 His men deserted him and onward he went\n
 He came to a place where the light was dull\n
 His forehead pounding in his skull\n
 Heavy heart was wracked with pain\n
 Insomnia raging in his brain\n
 Well he threw down his helmet and his cross-handled sword\n
 He renounced his faith, he denied his Lord\n
 Crawled on his belly, put his ear to the wall\n
 One way or another he\'d put an end to it all\n
 He leaned down, cut the electric wire \n
 Stared into the flames and he snorted the fire\n
 Peered through the darkness, caught a glimpse of the two\n
 It was hard to tell for certain who was who\n
 He lowered himself down on a golden chain\n
 His nerves were quaking in every vein\n
 His knuckles were bloody, he sucked in the air\n
 He ran his fingers through his greasy hair\n
 They looked at each other and their glasses clinked\n
 One single unit inseparably linked \n
 \“Got a strange premonition there\’s a man close by.\”\n
 \“Don\’t worry about him, he wouldn\’t harm a fly.\”\n
 From behind the curtain the boss crossed the floor\n
 He moved his feet and he bolted the door\n
 Shadows hiding the lines in his face\n
 With all the nobility of an ancient race\n
 She turned, she was startled with a look of surprise\n
 With a hatred that could hit the skies\n
 \“You\’re a reckless fool, I can see it in your eyes.\n
 To come this way was by no means wise.\”\n
 \“Get up, stand up, you greedy lipped wench\n
 And cover your face or suffer the consequence.\n
 You are making my heart full sick.\n
 Put your clothes back on double quick.\”\n
 \“Silly boy, you think me a saint.\n
 I\’ll listen no more to your words of complaint.\n
 You\’ve given me nothing but the sweetest lies.\n
 Now hold your tongue and feed your eyes.\”\n
 \“I\’d have given you the stars and the planets too\n
 But what good would these things do you?\n
 Bow the heart, if not the knee\n
 Or never again this world you\’ll see.\”\n
 \“Oh, please let not your heart be cold.\n
 This man is dearer to me than gold.\”\n
 \“Oh my dear, you must be blind.\n
 He\’s a gutless ape with a worthless mind.\”\n
 \“You had your way too long with me.\n
 Now it\’s me who\’ll determine how things shall be.\n
 Try to escape,\” he cussed and cursed\n
 \“You\’ll have to try to get past me first.\”\n
 \“I dare not let your passion rule.\n
 You think my heart, the heart of a fool.\n
 And you sir, you cannot deny \n
 You made a monkey of me, what and for why?\”\n
 \“I\’ll have no more of this insulting chat.\n
 The devil can have you, I\’ll see to that.\n
 Look sharp or step aside,\n
 Or in the cradle you\’ll wish you died.\”\n
 The gun went boom and the shot rang clear\n
 First bullet grazed his ear\n
 Second ball went right straight in\n
 And he bent in the middle like a twisted pin\n
 He crawled to the corner and he lowered his head\n
 He gripped the chair and he grabbed the bed\n
 It would take more than needle and thread\n
 Bleeding from the mouth, he\’s as good as dead\n
 \“You shot my husband down, you fiend.\”\n
 \“Husband, what husband, what the hell do you mean?\n
 He was a man of strife, a man of sin.\n
 I cut him down and I\’ll throw him to the wind.\”\n
 \“Hear this,” she said, with angry breath\n
 \“You too shall meet the lord of death.\n
 It was I who brought your soul to life.\”\n
 And she raised her robe and she drew out a knife\n
 His face was hard and caked with sweat\n
 His arms ached and his hands were wet\n
 \“You\’re a murderous queen and a bloody wife.\n
 If you don’t mind, I\’ll have the knife.\”\n
 \“We\’re two of a kind and our blood runs hot.\n
 But we\’re no way similar in body and thought.\n
 All husbands are good men, as all wives know.\”\n
 Then she pierced him to the heart and his blood did flow\n
 His knees went limp and he reached for the door\n
 His doom was sealed, he slid to the floor\n
 He whispered in her ear, \“This is all your fault.\n
 My fighting days have come to a halt.\”\n
 She touched his lip and kissed his cheek\n
 He tried to speak, but his breath was weak\n
 \“You died for me, now I\'ll die for you.\”\n
 She put the blade to her heart and she ran it through\n
 All three lovers together in a heap\n
 Thrown into the grave forever to sleep\n
 Funeral torches blazed away\n
 Through the towns and the villages all night and all day\n




    </string>
    <string name="tempestlyrics">

The pale moon rose in its glory\n
 Out on the western town\n
 She told a sad, sad story\n
 Of the great ship that went down\n

 \‘Twas the fourteen day of April\n
 Over the waves she rode\n
 Sailing into tomorrow\n
 To a golden age foretold\n

 The night was bright with starlight\n
 The seas were sharp and clear\n
 Moving through the shadows\n
 The promised hour was near\n

 Lights were holding steady\n
 Gliding over the foam\n
 All the lords and ladies\n
 Heading for their eternal home\n

 The chandeliers were swaying\n
 From the balustrades above\n
 The orchestra was playing\n
 Songs of faded love\n

 The watchman he lay dreaming\n
 As the ballroom dancers twirled\n
 He dreamed the Titanic was sinking\n
 Into the underworld\n

 Leo took his sketchbook\n
 He was often so inclined\n
 He closed his eyes and painted\n
 The scenery in his mind\n
 Cupid struck his bosom\n
 And broke it with a snap\n
 The closest woman to him\n
 He fell into her lap\n

 He heard a loud commotion\n
 Something sounded wrong\n
 His inner spirit was saying\n
 That he couldn’t stand here long\n

 He staggered to the quarterdeck\n
 No time now to sleep \n
 Water on the quarterdeck\n
 Already three foot deep\n

 Smokestack leaning sideways\n
 Heavy feet began to pound\n
 He walked into the whirlwind\n
 Sky spinning all around\n

 The ship was going under\n
 The universe opened wide\n
 The roll was called up yonder\n
 The angels turned aside\n

 Lights down in the hallway\n
 Flickering dim and dull\n
 Dead bodies already floating\n
 In the double bottomed hull\n

 The engines then exploded\n
 Propellers they failed to start\n
 The boilers overloaded\n
 The ship\'s bow split apart\n

 Passengers were flying\n
 Backward, forward, far and fast\n
 They mumbled, fumbled, tumbled\n
 Each one more weary than the last\n
 The veil was torn asunder\n
 \‘Tween the hours of twelve and one\n
 No change, no sudden wonder\n
 Could undo what had been done\n

 The watchman lay there dreaming\n
 At fourty-five degrees\n
 He dreamed the Titanic was sinking\n
 Dropping to her knees\n

 Wellington, he was sleeping\n
 His bed began to slide\n
 His valiant heart was beating\n
 He pushed the tables aside\n

 Glass of shattered crystal\n
 Lay scattered \‘round about\n
 He strapped on both his pistols \n
 How long could he hold out?\n

 His men and his companions\n
 Were nowhere to be seen\n
 In silence there he waited for\n
 Time and space to intervene\n

 The passageway was narrow\n
 There was blackness in the air\n
 He saw every kind of sorrow\n
 Heard voices everywhere\n

 Alarm bells were ringing\n
 To hold back the swelling tide\n
 Friends and lovers clinging\n
 To each other side by side\n

 Mothers and their daughters\n
 Descending down the stairs\n
 Jumped into the icy waters\n
 Love and pity sent their prayers\n

 The rich man, Mr. Astor\n
 Kissed his darling wife\n
 He had no way of knowing\n
 Be the last trip of his life\n

 Calvin, Blake and Wilson \n
 Gambled in the dark\n
 Not one of them would ever live to\n
 Tell the tale of disembark\n

 Brother rose up against brother\n
 In every circumstance\n
 They fought and slaughtered each other\n
 In a deadly dance\n

 They lowered down the lifeboats\n
 From the sinking wreck\n
 There were traitors, there were turncoats\n
 Broken backs and broken necks\n

 The bishop left his cabin\n
 To help all those in need\n
 Turned his eyes up to the heavens\n
 Said, “The poor are yours to feed.”\n

 Davey the brothel keeper\n
 Came out, dismissed his girls\n
 Saw the water getting deeper\n
 Saw the changing of his world\n

 Jim Dandy smiled\n
 He\'d never learned to swim\n
 Saw the little crippled child\n
 And he gave his seat to him\n

 He saw the starlight shining\n
 Streaming from the East\n
 Death was on the rampage\n
 But his heart was now at peace\n

 They battened down the hatches\n
 But the hatches wouldn\’t hold\n
 They drowned upon the staircase\n
 Of brass and polished gold\n

 Leo said to Cleo\n
 \“I think I\’m going mad.\”\n
 But he\'d lost his mind already\n
 Whatever mind he had\n

 He tried to block the doorway\n
 To save all those from harm\n
 Blood from an open wound\n
 Pouring down his arm\n

 Petals fell from flowers\n
 \‘Til all of them were gone\n
 In the long and dreadful hours\n
 The wizard’s curse played on\n

 The host was pouring brandy\n
 He was going down slow\n
 He stayed right \‘til the end\n
 He was the last to go\n

 There were many, many others\n
 Nameless here forevermore\n
 They\'d never sailed the ocean\n
 Or left their homes before\n

 The watchman, he lay dreaming\n
 The damage had been done\n
 He dreamed the Titanic was sinking\n
 And he tried to tell someone\n

 The captain, barely breathing\n
 Kneeling at the wheel\n
 Above him and beneath him\n
 Fifty thousand tons of steel\n

 He looked over at his compass\n
 And he gazed into its face\n
 Needle pointing downward\n
 He knew he lost the race\n

 In the dark illumination\n
 He remembered bygone years\n
 He read the Book of Revelation\n
 And he filled his cup with tears\n

 When the Reaper\’s task had ended\n
 Sixteen hundred had gone to rest\n
 The good, the bad, the rich, the poor\n
 The loveliest and the best\n

 They waited at the landing\n
 And they tried to understand\n
 But there is no understanding\n
 On the judgment of God’s hand\n

 News came over the wires\n
 And struck with deadly force\n
 Love had lost its fires\n
 All things had run their course\n

 The watchman he lay dreaming\n
 Of all things that can be\n
 He dreamed the Titanic was sinking\n
 Into the deep blue sea\n


    </string>
    <string name="rollonjohnlyrics">
Doctor, doctor, tell me the time of day\n
 Another bottle’s empty, another penny spent\n
 He turned around and he slowly walked away\n
 They shot him in the back and down he went\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 From the Liverpool docks to the red light Hamburg streets\n
 Down in the quarry with the Quarrymen\n
 Playing to the big crowds, playing to the cheap seats\n
 Another day in the life on your way to your journey’s end \n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 Sailing through the trade winds bound for the South\n
 Rags on your back just like any other slave\n
 They tied your hands and they clamped your mouth\n
 Wasn’t no way out of that deep, dark cave\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 I heard the news today, oh boy\n
 They hauled your ship up on the shore\n
 Now the city gone dark, there is no more joy\n
 They tore the heart right out and cut it to the core\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 Put down your bags and get ‘em packed\n
 Leave right now, you won’t be far from wrong\n
 The sooner you go, the quicker you’ll be back\n
 You been cooped up on an island far too long\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 Slow down, you’re moving way too fast\n
 Come together right now over me\n
 Your bones are weary, you’re about to breathe your last\n
 Lord, you know how hard that it can be\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 Roll on John, roll through the rain and snow\n
 Take the right hand road and go where the buffalo roam\n
 They’ll trap you in an ambush ‘fore you know\n
 Too late now to sail back home\n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n

 Tyger, tyger, burning bright\n
 I pray the Lord my soul to keep\n
 In the forest of the night\n
 Cover him over, and let him sleep \n

 Shine your light\n
 Move it on \n
 You burned so bright\n
 Roll on, John\n



    </string>
























</resources>